准备好了，亲爱的
Hey, love bug. You ready?
是的。
Oh, yeah.
- 你猜怎么着，妈妈。 - 什么
Hey, guess what, Mom? What?
我发现那里的黄蜂。
I figured out where wasps come from.
在哪里
Oh, yeah? Where?
那么，它必须是,,, 如果你把一只飞蛾在空气中，
Well, I think it must be,
把它变成一只黄蜂。
if you flick water into the air just right, it'll turn into a wasp.
- 好！ - 是的。
Hey! Yep.
- 学校怎么样 - 好吧。
That's cool.
So, how was your day at school?
我与小姐。巴特勒会议。 我喜欢他。
Fine.
I had a good meeting with Miss Butler this time. I kind of liked her.
说什么
What'd she say?
他说，没有entregabas任务。
Well, she said that you weren't turning in your homework assignments.
我说，“我知道，让 控制它的每一个夜晚。 “
And I told her, "I know he does them,
他说，他发现了几个 在你的背包底部的就业机会。
"'cause I check them every night."
She said she found a big chunk of them
crumpled up at the bottom of your backpack.
他问我是不是！
She didn't ask for 'em.
不必。 你只需要提供。
Baby, she doesn't have to. You're just supposed to turn them in.
并告诉我说，你继续找 全天的窗口。
And she said you're still staring out the window all day.
不是所有的一天！
Not all day.
而你摧毁了你的刀。
And she said that you destroyed her pencil sharpener.
这是不是故意的！
Not on purpose!
和几个石头你被困在。
Wait! She said that you crammed a bunch of rocks in it.
我想如果削尖的铅笔 我也可以磨刀石。
I thought if we could sharpen pencils,
maybe we could sharpen rocks.
你会怎么办 用锋利的石头吗
Well, what were you gonna do with a bunch of sharpened rocks?
我想使头 箭头我的收藏。
I was trying to make arrowheads for my rock collection.
Mm.
- 别碰我！ - 等待。
Dude, my turn!
Hold on.
梅森
Mason!
萨曼莎！
Samantha!
汤米！驴梅森是吗
Oh!
Tommy! ls Mason down there?
是的。
Yeah.
- 告诉他，他有和我共进晚餐。 - 行。
Well, tell him he has to come home to dinner.
Okay.
- 嗨。 - 你好，华丽。
Hey-
为什么不是你准备好了吗
Hey, sweetie. Why aren't you ready?
您好，梅森！
Hey, Mason.
嗨，蒂姆。
Hey,Ted.
- 快点，快点。 - 现在是几H
Come on, hurry up. Let's go.
九！来吧！
What time is it? It's 9:00. Let's go, let's go!
我想告诉你，贾尼丝 我失败了。我没有保姆。
Okay, I meant to call you, 'cause Janice flaked out.
你为什么不叫别人呢
I don't have a sitter.
我不能让 1现在。这是9。
Why didn't you call somebody else?
I can't get a babysitter now. It's 9:00.
但是你可以和我们呆在一起。
But you're welcome to hang out with us.
不！我们有计划。 你的朋友们都在等着我。
Well, no! I mean, we have plans.
The guys are expecting me.
- 好了，你看。 - 好。
Well, you can go. All right.
早在几个小时。
I'll come back in a couple of hours.
是不是好
Is that okay?
。是的，这一切都很好。
Yeah. Yes, it's okay. All right.
“回来！回来了！ 我不想说话马戈钱！ “
"'Turn back! Turn back! I don't wanna talk to Moaning Myrtle.'
“谁哈利表示，由于 兵荒马乱。 “
"'Who?' said Harry, as they backtracked quickly.
“经常出没的厕所之一 在女生浴室，赫敏说。 “
"'She haunts one of the toilets
"in the girls' bathroom on the first floor,' said Hermione.
“萦绕在厕所”
"'She haunts a toilet?'
“是的，它已经不在服务区 所有的一年，因为她生气,,,
'Yes, it's been out of order all year,
“而淹没一切”
"'because she keeps having tantrums and flooding the place!'
“就永远不会有 如果我能帮助它。 “
"'l never went in there anyway, if I could avoid it.'
“这太可怕了要做 尿尿，而她骂你！ “
"'It's awful trying to have a pee with her wailing at you."'
你为什么这么说
Why can't you just say that?
- 对不起。 -'re对不起。说谎。
I'm sorry.
我想在这里陪我的孩子,,,,,,
You're sorry, that's bullshit!
停止使用儿童作为借口
That's right. I wanna stay here with my kids.
That's what I'd rather do.
Would you stop using your kids as an excuse?
我知道你喜欢呆在这里。 这是没有必要的,,,
I know you have to stay here with your kids! You're acting...
什么都不知道！
You have this immature life. You have no responsibility!
没有责任！
I have an immature life!
í了我。不知道 这是什么意思是一个父亲。
I have responsibility. I have an immature life.
不知道！而我为什么 负责在生活中你的错误
You don't know what it's like to be a parent.
No, I don't!
And why am I responsible for your mistakes in life?
错误不叫我的孩子！
Don't call my kids mistakes! Don't!
我没有说他们,,,！
I didn't call your kids...
- 你说“你的错误”,,,,,, - 我知道我说的。
You said, "Your mistakes in your life," pointing at my kids.
您再次使用它们。
I know what I said, you know. And immediately you use your kids again.
是现实！我是一个母亲！
This is the reality. I'm a parent!
意味着责任。 í 喜欢有自己的时间
- That means responsibility. - I know you're a parent.
I would love to have some time to myself!
我很想去看看 一个他妈的电影！难道你不觉得吗
I would love to just go to a fuckin' movie!
外出就餐。去酒吧。
You don't think I'd like that?
他甚至不知道怎么办！
Go have some dinner, go to a bar!
她是某人的女儿， 现在我是谁的母亲！
I don't even know what that's like!
I was someone's daughter, then I was somebody's fuckin' mother!
你明白吗我不知道那是怎么样！
Okay? I don't know what that's like!
“我想我再次做到了，
“我打了你的心脏我 我输了比赛。 “
“哦，宝贝，宝贝 哎呀！ ,,,,,,你以为我是在恋爱，
“已被送往从上面，
Stop!
- 够了！ - “我不是无辜的。”
够了！
Quit it!
“你看，我的问题是这样的。 我是在做梦。 “
- “祝各位大侠的存在。” - 够了！
Quit it!
我哭了，看着天。 我在很多方面是傻瓜“
Mom!
这是怎么回事
What the hell is going on in here?
你知道现在是什么时间
Do you guys know what time it is?
他,,,,,,扔东西！
He's throwing things at me.
梅森！你的妹妹，不要乱扔东西。
Mason! Do not throw things at your sister!
烈。她打了我第一次。
She's faking, she hit me first!
听他们两个！
Listen, both of you!
我要回去睡觉了。我不想听 没有声音这里了一个多小时。
I'm going back to bed.
I don't wanna hear another peep out of here for an hour.
的睡眠！
Go to sleep.
- 假的！ - 嘿！
- Faker! - Guys!
Awesome!
你看我发现了什么在街上。
Look what I found in the street.
Dude!
这是很好的，对吗
I know, right?
看看这些！
Look at those.
哎呀！看看这些！
Ooh! Look at those!
Awesome!
好吧，听,,,
So listen, guys, I wanna talk to you about something.
我想谈，并,,,
And you might not like this idea at first,
可能不喜欢它 这个想法在第一，但,,,
but we're moving to Houston.
搬到休斯顿。
When?
什么时候
Well, soon.
不久。之前，我们应该做的 首先，以避免支付2租金。
We should be out by the first,
不，妈妈，没有移动。 不，不。对不起，妈妈。不，不。
so we don't have to pay two rents next month.
No, Mother, we're not moving. Nope,nope.
Sorry, Mom. Nope.Nope.
萨曼莎，我要回 大学以改善我们的生活。
Samantha, I have to go back to college,
我的工作我不能 养家，因为我想要的。
so I can make us a better living.
With this job, I can't take care of us the way I'd like to.
我不能去。
I can't keep going this way.
奶奶会帮助我们。
And Grandma said she'd help us out,
这将是很好的是她的身边。
and it would be nice to be near her.
好吧，妈妈。你可以做什么 随时随地。但我们不会移动。
Fine, Mother.
You can do whatever you want,
but we're not moving.
那我们的朋友呢
And what about our friends?
我们将通过电子邮件或信函。 我们可以回去看望。
Oh, baby, we can email them or write.
We can come back to visit.
你猜我们发现这个地方 奶奶将自己的房间。
And guess what?
This place that Grandma found us,
you'll each have your own room. Right?
这是怎么回事
And there's a pool.
并有一个水池。
妈妈，你还爱爸爸
Mom, do you still love Dad?
我还是爱你的父亲。
I still love your father,
但是，这并不意味着 曾经健康的呆在一起。
but that doesn't mean it was healthy for us to stay together.
如果，这一举动后， 他找不到我们
What if after we move he's trying to find us and he can't?
这不会是一个问题。
Oh, that won't be a problem.
你可以叫奶奶。
He can call Grandma and she'll tell him,
或拨打号码的信息。
or he can call Information.
我们会很容易找到。
We won't be hard to find.
你还在阿拉斯加
Is he still in Alaska?
因此，你的叔叔说。
Well, that's what your uncle says.
驯服北极熊什么的。
Probably taming polar bears or something.
我希望熊驯服他。
Yeah. Well, I hope they're taming him.
家具移动和存储
- 这里。要帮忙吗 - 清除。
Here, wanna help me out?
拿起画,,, 仔细,,,
Sure.
Okay. Take this paint very carefully
油漆和着色剂，标记或点,,,
and paint any little smudge or mark or anything
插座，门后,,,
on the baseboard there,
和入口的整个内部。
behind the door and all around the doorways on the inside.
他说，他将前来参观。
She says we're gonna come visit
我会写信给你打电话。
and I'm gonna write and call you.
等一下。 还有在其他线路上的呼叫。
Oh, wait, hold on a second. I'm getting another call.
喂
Hello?
对不起，汤米。梅森不 你可以走到今天。我们正在搬家。
Sorry, Tommy.
Mason can't come over today. We're moving.
我在其他线路。再见。
And I'm on the other line.
Bye.
驴索菲亚
Althea?
我给你的指令 为侦察兵。
I'm gonna be sending Sailor Scout instructions.
响应并告诉我如何 是其他侦察兵。
Email and write back telling me how the other scouts are doing.
因为现在你的本金。
Well,because you're the leader now.
来吧。我想获得 天黑之前。
Okay, let's go, 'cause I wanna get there before it gets dark.
再见花园！ 再见灌木丛！再见邮箱！
Goodbye, yard. Goodbye, crape myrtle. Goodbye, mailbox.
东东妈妈再见箱 不让我们走，不想拍。
Goodbye, box of stuff Mommy won't let us take with us,
再见了房子。我永远不会爱你的妈妈 和以前一样的让我们感动！
but we don't wanna throw away.
Goodbye, house.
I'll never like Mommy as much for making us move!
萨曼莎！你为什么不说再见 也是低劣的态度呢
Samantha!
Why don't you say goodbye to that little horseshit attitude, okay?
不要登高车程。
'Cause we're not taking that in the car.
再见老太太听 摇滚乐摩托车和步行。
Goodbye, old lady who listens to rock music and rides a motorcycle.
嘿！
OLIVIA; Hey!
怎么样了 够了！把分离。
What's happening back there? Stop, put the barrier up.
放一个枕头在他们之间。 做一个屏障。而这就足够了。
Hey! Put the pillow between you.
Make a barrier, come on. Stop.
我们会玩一种叫做 “沉默的比赛。”
We're gonna play a game called The Game of Silence.
这是 更安静的时间获胜。
Whoever can stay quiet for the longest period of time wins.
你认为你可以做什么
You guys think you can do that?
来吧！
Okay, go.
该路公交车到达十分钟。
The bus will be here in 10 minutes.
把这些职责的背包。
Put that homework in your backpack.
吃！
Go eat!
亲爱的，去吃饭！
Baby, go eat.
我要去！
I am!
说英语！
Speak English!
住口！
Shut up! Mom!
妈妈！他说话 语言是愚蠢了。
She's speaking that stupid language again!
萨曼莎！
Samantha!
他说话很清晰的英语，妈妈。
I was speaking perfectly clear English, Mother.
你知道这是一个有点慢头。
He's a little slow in the head.
官方不及格一年级。
He did officially flunk first grade.
- 支持你的屁股。 - 是呀，先生的母亲！
Sit your butt down!
好了，我要你听。
Yes, sir, Mother, sir!
奶奶的要找到一所学校。
All right, listen up, guys. Grandma's gonna pick you up after school.
他的父亲来了这一天。 他们将在下午与他。
Your dad's in town for the day.
你会来住在这里
So you're gonna spend the afternoon with him.
Oh. Is he moving back?
我不知道。
I don't know.
八年前，还没有见过他。
We haven't seen him in about 80 years.
此外家伙,,,,,,一年半。
Like a year and a half.
请。
Ha-ha!
你可以吃 公交车来了。
Oh, please.
Can we please eat here? The bus is coming.
任何人都希望药水
Who wants syrup?
那个！良好的斜体字。
All right, nice cursive.
好了，梅森。当控制 模块，我会找到你的吗
Okay, Mason, when I check the mobiles, am I gonna find yours?
- 第 - 为什么不呢
No.
因为我还没有说完。
And why not?
现在是时候结束了。
'Cause I didn't finish it.
分！
Well, it's time to finish it.
不，这样做:“苹果，戒”。
Just a minute.
No, let's do... Apple Quit.
时间来完成你的工作，梅森！
Time to finish your work, Mason. "Apple Quit."
苹果，戒了！
这是我的历史考验。
- So this is my history test. Mmm-hmm.
十大祝贺，太棒了！
"A+", very good.
而这又是一个历史的考验
And that's another history test.
而另一位“10。”
Mmm-hmm. And another
还有就是祝贺。强悍。
Yeah, it doesn't have a plus, but, oh, well.
这就是我的报告,,,蜥蜴。
And then, um, that's my report on lizards.
让我看看你的图纸。
Oh. Let me see your pictures.
右。这是我的画。
Oh, yeah. These are my pictures.
- 那是什么 - 他的名字是吉尔。
What is that?
- 吉尔 - 是的。
Well, that's called a dewlap.
这是数学考试。
A dewlap, okay.
十年了吗
Oh, yeah, this is a math test.
梅森！这是 最后的糖果，对不对
CATHERINE; Oh, "A" again.
Mase, that's the last candy,okay?
没关系。
Okay-
当你表现出的东西,,,
We need to put this stuff up.
这是他。
That's him.
Daddy!
我的天啊！
Oh, my God! Look at you, you're so big!
他们是如此之大！
Hey, NU.
好吧，伙计 难道他们想玩得开心吗
What's happenin', buddy?
Huh? You guys ready to have some fun?
Yeah!
Yeah! All right.
- 凯瑟琳，你怎么样 - 好吧。
Hey, Catherine, how are you? Mase, I'm good.
我很高兴。我应该带什么时候
Mmm, good to see you. Yeah.
What time should I have these rascals back?
我想说7:30。 我要带他们回家。
Oh, I don't know, around 7:30, I guess.
为什么不采取 我对他从他的母亲呢
I gotta get them home by 8:00.
Oh, you know what, why don't I take 'em over to their mom's?
她希望我。
No, that's okay. She's expecting me.
没问题。 你知道得到的，对不对
No, that's all right. You guys know where it is, don't you?
我会的。没问题。
Oh, yeah. All right. I'll do it. It's no problem.
- 不是一个好主意。 - 没问题。行
I don't think that's such a good idea.
你准备好了吗
Look, it's no problem. All right?
一会儿！ 他们不得不随身携带的东西。
You guys ready to go? Let's do it, go!
Go? Wait a minute. You gotta get your stuff.
你的背包，你的钱包。 该任务。去洗手间。
You got backpack, your purse,
令人惊讶他们是如何成长！
homework, go to the bathroom.
Can't believe how big they are.
时间在流逝。
Yeah. Time's going by.
我们希望让他们在这里在休斯敦。
Must be nice for you, having 'em here in Houston.
我的爱，是的。 我志愿在学校。
I love it, yeah. I'm volunteering at their school.
真的吗你会怎么做呢
Yeah? What you doing over there?
我是在图书馆。 我读的小家伙。
I'm in the library. You know, reading to the little ones.
有什么好！
Oh, great.
所以，阿拉斯加，是吗
So, Alaska, huh?
是的。
Yeah.
你住在哪里
Are you back?
我们会看到。
We'll see.
怎么丽芙
How's Liv?
忙。
She's a busy girl.
他回到了大学。
She's back in school.
同时工作，抚养两个孩子。
But she's working and single parenting.
A lot to juggle.
你拥有了一切
- You guys got everything? - Yeah.
告别奶奶。
All right, say goodbye to your grandmother.
- 再见！ - 我在途中！
Bye, Grandma.
一会儿,,,,,,
All right, let's roll. Uh, no, wait a second.
你不喜欢 礼物，对不对
You're not the type of kids who like presents, are you?
- 是的！ - 不，你,,,
Yes! No, you don't.
礼物真的吗来吧！
Of course we do. Presents? Really? Let's do it!
Yay!
- 我要去！ - 我想去！
I call front seat!
梅森在向外的旅程 和萨曼莎在后面。
I wanted the front seat, though.
All right. Well, Mason gets it on the way there
顶部。
and Samantha gets it on the way back.
- 安全带！ - 腰带。当然！
- Hop in there. - Seat belts!
不要忘记带。
Seat belts. All right. Seat belts.
无论是有这个汽车座椅。
Don't forget your seat belts.
It's not like this car has any seat belts.
Mmm...
好吧。好吧。好吧！
Nice. Nice. Nice!
很好！
Come here, come here, yes!
过来！是的！
Oh, that was awesome!
这是真棒！
Get up there, Mason! Get up there! It was so good!
现在的你，梅森，倒是你！ 这是非常不错的！
Come on.
来吧！
Let 'em know who you are, buddy.
告诉他们谁 是你，朋友。我告诉了他。
Let 'em know who you are.
Mwah!
是的！是的！
Yes! Yes! Yes!
是的！
All right. All right, don't worry about it.
没关系。不用担心。
Wish we could use the bumpers.
我想我已经座无虚席。
Bumpers are for kids!
该站是儿童。 你有两年的时间
What are you, two years old?
他们所服务的停止。 生活不给你盖。
You don't want the bumpers.
Life doesn't give you bumpers.
他来了！现在！
There we, there we go. There we go! We got something there!
任何事情都会发生！
We got something! We got something!
Oh!
上一次我已经收拾好。 这是更有趣。
Last time I went bowling, we had bumpers and it was a lot more fun!
他们所服务的停止。
You don't want the bumpers, all right?
是所有玩低 停止，这意味着什么。
You bowl a strike with the bumpers
and it doesn't mean anything.
相信我。
Trust me.
里只存得很好。
Just lay it out on the lane.
一,,,,,,二,,,,,,三，,,,
One, two, three and...
VIVA EL的父亲！
Let's hear it for the father!
Boom!
- Get up there! - Great shot!
Get out there, girl!
四黑水员工们 野蛮攻击费卢杰。
Four Blackwater operatives have been viciously attacked
叛军放火 尸体和汽车，并,,,
in their cars in Fallujah.
The bodies and cars were set on fire after insurgents started...
看到了吗这是一场灾难。
Look at this! It's a disaster.
我会告诉你什么是发生在伊拉克。
Let me tell you what's happening in Iraq, all right?
正是每个人 想着我就知道会发生什么。
Exactly what every thinking person in the world
knew was gonna happen before they got started.
à布什和球迷谁 围绕他们该死。
But Bush and his little numb-nut fanatics he's got around him,
25分！
they don't give a rat's ass.
什么
That's a quarter.
你说“他妈的”。
What's a quarter?
宽恕。
You said A-S-S.
Oh, sorry. My bad.
我的老师说，这是一场正义战争 因为预防胜于治疗。
And my teacher says it's a good war,
because it's better to be safe than sorry.
难道这就是他们教你吗 听你的父亲。
That's what they're teaching you in school?
All right. Listen to me. Listen to your father, okay?
这是一个谎言。这是天大的谎言。
That is the lie. That's the big lie.
伊拉克无关，与什么 双塔。我知道，对不对
Iraq had nothing to do with what happened at the World Trade Center.
我想。
You know that, right?
由谁来定投，乔丹
I guess.
Who you gonna vote for next fall, MJ?
- 我不知道。 - 你可以不选。有18岁。
I don't know.
He can't vote. He's not 18.
你投谁的
All right, who would you vote for?
- 佩里 - 任何人，但布什！行
Kerry?
Anybody but Bush! Okay?
你会回来住在这里
Are you gonna move back?
这就是我想要的。 我需要找工作。
Uh, I'm planning on it. You know, I gotta find a job.
你永远都挂出了妈
Are you and Mom gonna get back together?
我不知道。不,,,,,,只是取决于我。
I don't know.
That's not, uh, entirely up to me, you know?
我记得当我六岁。 你和妈妈像是疯了。
I remember when I was six,
you and Mom were fighting like mad.
你叫得那么大声和母亲哭了。
You were yelling so loud and she was crying.
是，你还记得吗
That's what you remember, huh?
是的。
Yep-
你不记得了加尔维斯顿旅游
You don't remember the trips to Galveston,
而当我们在扎营 大弯和有乐趣
camping in Big Bend, all the fun we had?
号
Nope.
- 你有没有生气，你妈妈呢 - 是的。
You ever get mad at your mother?
- 那你的兄弟吗 - 是的！
Yeah.
- 他们有你哭了 - 是的，当然。
You ever get mad at your brother?  Yeah.
Yeah. You ever yell at him? Oh, yeah.
但是，这并不意味着 不想要的，不是吗
Doesn't mean you don't love him, right?
当你是一个成年人了同样的情况。
Mmm...
Look, the same thing happens when you're grown up, all right?
你生气的人。 没什么重要的。
You know, you get mad at people.
You know, it's not a big deal.
你在阿拉斯加做什么
What'd you do in Alaska?
我曾经在船上,,,一会,,,
I worked on a boat for a while. Um...
我试着谱曲。
I tried to write some music.
你有没有看到一只北极熊
Did you see any polar bears?
没有，但我看到了科迪亚克熊。 在他妈的是巨大的！
No. But I saw a Kodiak bear.
爸爸！他们是50美分 用这个词！
It was fuckin' huge!
Dad! That's 50 cents for the F-word!
宽恕。
I'm sorry.
拿一块钱。留着零钱吧。
Here, take a dollar, all right? Keep the change.
我将现在看到的更加频繁。
You guys are gonna be seeing a lot more of me. Okay?
我错过了很多。我想让他们知道。
I missed you two real bad while I was gone, okay, I want you to know that.
我需要自己的时间。
I just needed to take some time, you know, to...
你妈妈，我,,,
Just“
Your mom and me, okay...
他的母亲,,,,,,是,,,,,,很难。
Well, your mother, okay, is a piece of work, all right.
我想他们知道。
I think you know that by now, all right?
而我,,,,,,我很高兴 与你同在2。
And I'm just...
而遗憾的停止的问题。
I'm so happy to be with the two of you, okay?
我觉得我比这更好的。是不是好
And I'm sorry about that bumper business.
I'm gonna get better at stuff like that, okay?
这是我在滴水泉发现 罗迪和,,,我的朋友给了我这个。
I got that one at Dripping Springs,
and, um, my friend Rodney gave me that one.
- 我买了它。 - 你买了吗
- Yeah? - And I bought that one.
- 你有没有发现她的滴水泉 - 是的。
You bought this one? Yeah.
You found this at Dripping Springs? Uh-huh.
辣妹！还有什么你得到了什么
Wow.
这些蛇的椎骨。
What else do you got?
Well, um, these are snake vertebrae.
蛇驴脊椎骨呸！
Snake vertebrae? That's disgusting. Huh?
梅森，我不希望你来收集 多个椎骨蛇。
Mason, I don't want you collecting snake vertebrae anymore.
- 这是我送你的笔吗 - 是的。
Is this the feather l sent you?
爸爸！我忘了告诉你 这些照片,,,,,,篮球。
Yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah, it is.
Oh, Dad! Um, l forgot to show you, um, these basketball pictures.
- 你是一个篮球队 - 是的。
You're on a basketball team? Yeah.
有什么好！
Wow! Check you out!
- 看看河狸的爪子。 - 爪水獭
These are beaver claws. Beaver claws?
驴任务海狸
That's me.
Yeah. No. MASON What, you hunting beaver?
You see, that's McKinney, that's Meg and that's Gem.
你踢什么位置
Those are my friends. Uh-huh.
基地。
What position do you play?
这是加拿大的解剖草。
Um, guard.
- 你的分数 - 8到10场比赛。
This is dried Canadian grass. Uh-huh.
Wait, have you scored any points?
驴8-10不可思议！
Well, about eight or 10 a game.
Eight or 10 a game? That is awesome!
有一次，他没有得分点，哭了起来。
Once, she didn't score any and she cried!
- 你有没有哭 - 一点。
You cried?
Well, only a little bit. Aw...
嗨！
Hello! Pomegranate.
梅森！妈妈来了！
Oh, Mason, Mom's home!
- 妈妈来了！ - 达到妈妈。
Mom's home!
Mom's home.
妈妈！嗨！
Mom! Hi! Look at this owl Daddy gave me!
看到猫头鹰í 他给了爸爸。是不是好
Isn't it cool? See, its head spins!
头部旋转。看手镯。 由印度人在阿拉斯加。
And look at this bracelet. It was made by Indians in Alaska.
爸爸给了我这个熊 雕刻手工，这提基。
And Daddy made this cool hand-carved grizzly bear and this tiki.
这是一个图腾。
- It's a totem. - And guess what else?
你猜！我们打保龄球 并有四个完美的镜头！
We went bowling and I made four strikes!
我们可以骑在爸爸的车。
Yeah, and we got to ride around in Dad's car! Wow.
- 嘿，丽芙。 - 嗨。
Hey, Liv. Hey.
我知道你想要的 让他们听到你的母亲。
I know you wanted me to drop them off at your mom's.
我想它会更容易在这里。
I just thought it'd be easier if I brought 'em over here.
你毁了我的计划。
Well, it really screwed up my plans.
- 我们想展示的房间。 - 是的。
Well, we just wanted to show him our rooms.
你吃什么
Yeah.
吃薯条 在保龄球馆。
Did you guys eat anything?
Well, we had some French fries at the bowling alley.
- 你有没有做功课 - 第 - 还没有。
Did you do your homework?
我可以和你谈谈之外的第二个
No. Not yet.
Okay. Can I talk to you outside for a second?
是的，当然。
Yeah. Sure.
他们吃更多的薯条。
They had more than French fries.
你认为他会留过夜吗
Do you think he's gonna spend the night?
显然不是。
Doesn't look like it.
一个非条件刺激， 一些生产,,,
Okay. An unconditioned stimulus,
没有学问的反应， 非自愿而不是制约。
something that produces an unlearned,
involuntary, unconditioned response.
什么是刺激二手 巴甫洛夫在他的实验
Now, in Pavlov's experiment,
what was the stimulus that he used?
来吧！是很难 一周什么肉！
Come on now, people! Tough weekend? What's the deal here?
肉类。或者更确切地说，肉粉。
Meat, right? Meat. Meat powder, actually.
不管是什么灰尘 肉，它的工作与你的狗。
Whatever meat powder is, it worked on this dog.
他把肉粉和生产 无条件的回应,,,
Okay, he put the meat powder in there
and it produced an unconditioned response in the dog, which was?
狗是垂涎三尺,,,！
Salivation! All right?
行
Now, who can give me another example
谁可以给我的另一个例子 无条件响应于刺激,,,
of an unconditioned stimulus response pair
每天都在发生。
that happens to you every day?
也许这是发生 任你了。
It's probably happening to some of you right now.
那么做爱
How about sex?
来到一个有吸引力的成员 异性有,,,
Sure, you know,
you see an attractive member of the opposite gender,
自动响应。 甚至没有去想它。
you have an automatic response.
米克・贾格尔写了一首歌:
You don't have to think about it.
Mick Jagger wrote a song about it.
“哦，当你被点名流涎 就像巴甫洛夫的狗。 “
"Oh, when they call your name,
"I salivate like a Pavlov dog."
非常感谢。尾类的。
Thank you very much. Class dismissed.
Welbrock博士。
Doctor Welbrock.
这是我的儿子，梅森。
This is my son Mason. Oh...
梅森，这是Welbrock博士。
Mason, this is Dr. Welbrock.
你的儿子！我还以为是个天才 谁参加了我班的孩子。
Your son.
Now see, I thought this was a boy genius
who was taking my college course.
他身体不舒服，所以我带了。
He wasn't feeling well today,so l thought I'd bring him with me.
无发热。这是一个骗局。
Uh...
我知道，因为我的儿子 9年他总是这样。
No fever. It's a con job.
I can tell because I have a nine-year-old son, he pulls this all the time.
同样的事情。
Same kind of deal.
- 你踢足球吗 - 第
Hey, you play soccer? No.
我的儿子不是。他讨厌足球。 他喜欢电脑。
Neither does my boy. He hates soccer. He likes computers.
我女儿喜欢它11 足球。谁了解呢
My 11-year-old daughter loves soccer!
也许我们可以参加我们的某个时候。
Who can figure?
Maybe we can get all you guys together sometime, huh?
也许，是的。
Maybe, yeah.
- 你准备好了吗 - 是的。
Well, you ready to go?
- 尼斯，梅森。 - 尼斯。
Yeah.
Nice to meet you, Mason. Nice to meet you, too.
并谢谢大家给我的课。
And thanks for coming to my class.
奥利维亚。
Olivia.
- 可爱的孩子。 - 谢谢！
Nice kid. Thanks.
你觉得奶奶会 可以照顾孩子吗
So, you think, uh, Grandma might be available for a little babysitting?
也许吧。
Maybe.
- 真的吗 - 是的。
Really? Oh, yeah.
WELBROCK Well, great.
唤醒死人了！
Dead man, dead man, wake up!
1，2，3，4，5，你还活着！
One, two, three, four, five, you're alive!
别碰我！
My turn. Kids, they're here!
伙计们！他们来了！
- They're home, they're home! - Come on!
快，快！
Hurry, hurry.
欢迎新人
Hi! Hi!
Oh! We're here!
我们回来了！
How was it? How was it? Hey! We've returned!
- 我很想念你！ - 嘿，爸爸！
Honey, it's so good to see you.
萨曼莎，梅森，谢谢！
Hi, Dad! Samantha, Mason. Hello.
Thank you. That's very nice.
Hey, Mom. How are you?
Oh! Mom, Mom!
萨曼莎和我做到了一个人。
They give you trouble? Look at the sign we made.
- Samantha and I made it all ourselves. - Yeah.
我知道男人不走那么高。
I know the boys helped you with that a lot.
No, not at all!
à分发礼物！
Okay. There you go.
Pass out the goodies. This is for the girls.
Don't worry, we got you some absinthe. It's in the...
我们需要一个巨大的提升。热门 全部扔纸飞机。
Let's pour.
You take this big elevator up,
and when we got to the top,
发生了什么事
we flew a paper airplane off.
它飞走！
- And what happened? - It flew!
他飞到几公里。
It flew away, it went for miles.
Went under the Arc de Triomphe, you know.
他们将在亲吻 叹息桥
Oh, did you guys kiss under the Bridge of Sighs?
- 是的。 - 我们做到了。
Yes. Yes, we did.
- 妈妈，我们能看到你的戒指 - 清除。
Mom, can we see your wedding ring?
Oh, sure.
这是一个阶梯环， 周围环绕着明亮的缩影。
WOW.
Technically, that's a fancy step cut
surrounded by miniature brilliant.
- 我希望我们能去欧洲。 - 是的。
I wish we could've gone to Europe.
我们去为家人下一次。
Yeah.
没有太大的损失。 我们在酒店,,,
Yeah, we'll go as a family next time.
But you didn't miss much, really.
玩电子游戏。
We just stayed in the hotel room
真的吗
the whole time playing video games.
与经济型酒店 很年轻，很老了。
Really?
And the hotels are really small and really old.
难道我帮你什么吗 你想要的甜点菜单
Squeaky.
Can I get you anything else?
我说躺着不起来。 把它放在你的钱包，请。
Would you like to see a dessert menu?
Listen, I told you to put that away.
小游戏在桌子上。
Would you put that in your purse, please?
另一瓶酒，请。
Computer games at the table. Yes, uh, please, another bottle of wine.
的炼焦。
- Um, Coke. - Um, you know what?
梅森，你没事了水。 只是可口可乐。谢谢。
Mason, you're okay with water.
而你呢 你完成你的科学项目
No more Cokes. Thank you.
And how about you? Did you finish your science project?
还没。
Not quite yet.
你有没有工作驴你建 什么什么的，你打算
Well, did you work on it? Did you build anything or plan anything or...
- 一点。 - 你做任何事情，柯以敏
A little. Did he work on it at all, Mindy?
号
No.
你坐在那里，梅森 和小游戏所有的时间
Did he sit around playing video games with Mason the whole time?
是的。
- Yeah. - Mmm.
你必须完成 我回来之前。
You were supposed to finish that by the time I got back.
你还记得吗
Remember?
Hey-
- Grevious是最好的。 - 尤达！尤达！
Grievous is the best, man.
Yoda! No, Yoda is, man!
- 有四条胳膊！ - 尤达！
Yoda! Yoda, man.
He has four arms.
奥迪奥小姐。 Burnsley。 每个人都认为这是一个女同性恋。
Yoda, represent!
I hate Miss Burnsby. Everybody's been saying she's lesbian.
是的。故建议斯泰西。
She is. She hit on Stacey.
- 呸！ - 是真的吗
Man, that's gross.
总是走来走去了更衣室。
Think it's true?
She's always walking in the locker room.
我觉得我看到了一对夫妇的,,,
I think I still have a couple of those...
保罗！告诉我们一个玩笑。
Hey, Paul, tell us a joke.
他妈的！他妈的！ 你他妈的！屁股！
Damn. Fuck. Go to hell. Ass.
- 我给你！ - 这是不公平的。
Oh! Blew you up.
Heck, man. That was not fair.
是的，它是。这是更公正的世界。
No, actually it was.
That's, like, the fairest thing ever.
Where are you?
是的！我再一次得到了。
Ooh, once again, I take you down.
请问面具
MASON'. The Mask?
做三剑客
Uh... Three Musketeers?
第一个字。
First word.
- 鸡 - 鸡。
- Chicken. Bird. - Chicken. Bird.
第二个字。
Second word.
- 连帽衫。 - 大发,,,罗宾汉！
Hood. Big hair. Robin Hood! Ah!
Brilliant child!
第二个字。
Second word.
驴曼塔
MINDY; Blanket?
道具，不！
Hey, you can't use props!
谈法官。没有道具。 你不能使用道具。
Hey,hey,hey!
Cut it out. Judges speak. No props. No props.
你可以不说。想想吧！
Can't use props. You can do it without that. Think, think, think.
移动,,,,,,目击者
- Um, folding. - Bunch!
The Gathered? Folded. Is it like... Um...
折叠,,,
lt's just messing around with a blanket. Wrinkling it...
东西用毯子。
- 破解,,, - 在时间裂缝！
A Wrinkle In Time! Wrinkle.
哈利・波特 与死出售
Whoo!
What are the guards of Azkaban?
Dementors. Ah...
你准备好了吗
Front of the line, are you ready?
算在一起，女士们 嘉宾:10 ,,,,,, 9 ,,,,,, 8 ,,,,,, 7 ,,,,,,
Count down with me, ladies and gentlemen. Ten!
Nine! Eight! Seven!
6 ,,, 5 ,,, 4 ,,, 3 ,,, 2 ,,, 1 ,,,
Six! Five! Four!
Three! Two! One!
来吧！
Let's go!
Whoo!
Thank you.
Thanks.
All righty. Here we go.
不，不，不。返回 和实践的第一个打击。
No, no, no. Back up and take a practice swing first, remember?
轻轻的。 扫地，扫地。
Nice and easy. Sweep the floor. Sweep the floor.
为好。
That's good.
不要重创。 总是打太辛苦。
Don't swing too hard, Randy.
He always swings too hard.
很好！
Hey! All right! Very good!
你的脚再往前追溯。
Back your feet up a little bit. Yeah, like that.
为好。现在，你可以打直。
Now you're gonna hit it straighter. Okay.
命中。软敲 和缓慢将是最适合你的。
All right, go up and hit it. That's good.
Nice slow swing is gonna be better for you.
很好！
All right!
你,,,你的脚 太开放，兰迪！
I don't know, man, you must've been...
See, your feet are too open, Randy.
当然。
Nice and natural.
是的！很好！
Yes! Go! All right!
高五。 良好的推杆，儿子，好推。
Give me five! Good putt, son, good putt.
你看到了，兰迪做到这一点。
Did you see that, Randy? That's the way to do it!
推杆的小鸟！
All right.
Birdie putt.
他妈的！
God damn it. Son of a bitch.
王八蛋！
Get my clubs, would you? Get the ball.
你会带给我棒去拿到球。
我们若游客这个周末。
This is just in case we have guests this weekend.
他总是说， 但从来没有游客。
He always says that, but we never have guests.
萨曼莎，我想你有你的爸爸。
Samantha, I think I heard your dad pull up.
好吧。
All right.
难道他们做完家务
You guys finish your chores?
不是所有的。
Not quite.
差不多。
Just about.
驴你拿着粉，山姆
How about the dusting, Sam?
还没。
I haven't done that yet.
我看见你和你的艺术项目。
Well, I saw you working on your art project.
你有时间来完成 但不适合你的工作
You had time to finish your little art project,
我以为我们已经谈过。
but you didn't have time to finish your chores?
我可以去除灰尘。
I thought we talked about that.
不，你有你自己的 任务和山姆有他。
Dad, it's fine, I can finish the dusting.
No, it's not fine, Mindy.
You have your own chores to do and Sam has hers to do.
很简单！
Huh? It's simple.
错误的决定，山姆。
Poor choice there, Sam. And hurry up.
梅森！
Mason!
他到达你的爸爸。
Your dad's here.
没有眩目的速度，对不对
You guys aren't setting any speed records, are you?
如何做请问一半诶！
What'd you do, get about half done? Hey, hey, hey.
- 他们完成了吗 - 第
So, did you finish?
No.
任务完成了
Is the job complete?
你会做什么明天
So, what are you gonna be doing tomorrow?
- 同样的，对不对 - 是的。
Same thing, right?
进来了。
Yeah. Okay. Go.
再见了，妈妈。
Bye, Mom.
再见了亲爱的。我爱你。
Bye,babe, I love you.
- 再见了，妈妈。 - 再见了，小丫头。
Bye, Mama.
- 有乐趣你的父亲。 - 等一下，梅森。
Bye, honey. Have fun with your dad.
Just a minute, Mason.
男孩并没有与叶结束。 萨曼莎未与尘埃结束,,,
The boys didn't finish raking leaves.
Samantha did not finish dusting.
所以，明天，当他们回来时，
So tomorrow, when they come home,
而不是游泳或其他 自己喜欢的东西做的，
instead of swimming and all the other
- 他们将完成他们的功课，好吗 - 是的。
little stuff that they want to do,
嗯，我说的。你明白吗
they're going to do their chores. Right?
Right.
Okay, guys, you had this conversation,
you understand? Tomorrow?
谢谢。寻求您的支持 不能是唯一一个谁大叫。
Okay-
Thank you. I just wanted you to back me up on that
so I'm not the only one yelling at them all the time.
我支持。得到它
Okay, I back you up. You guys got that?
每个人都同意吗明天，任务,,,
We all agree, everybody agrees, right? Tomorrow, chores?
我没听到。莱斯进入 一个耳朵出。
They don't hear it. Goes in one ear and out the other.
爸爸没有任何意义上的灰尘。
But, Dad, I mean, dusting is pointless.
是的是的。 它只是你不喜欢它。
It's not pointless, you just don't like to do it.
谁花今天的掸子
But, I mean, who dusts anymore?
你当我们告诉你！
You do when we ask you to!
奥利维亚，不要让我的答案 而在其他的前面。谢谢。
And don't... Olivia, don't let her back talk me
萨曼莎，请,,,
in front of the other kids, please. Thank you.
Samantha, please.
随你。
Whatever!
再见。传球非常好。
Bye-bye. Have a wonderful weekend.
再见，伙计们。我爱你。
Sam...
Okay. Bye, guys. Love you.
很抱歉，但我们谈的。有 画一条线和强硬。
I'm sorry, but I thought we talked about it.
You have to draw a line, you have to back it up.
是的，这是,,, 有很多线路，比尔。
Okay. It's just you have so many lines, Bill.
一切都在网上。
Everything's a line.
嗨，兰迪！嗨，伙计们。
Hey, Randy! Hey.
怎么你们俩
Bye. Bye.
我前进。
Hey, you two. How you doing?
Shotgun. Ooh!
- 我寄了。你还好吗，亲爱的 - 是的。
Here, let me get these bags here.
You doing okay, darling?
- 而你，冠军 - 我很好。
Yeah. Yeah?
What about you, cowboy? Pretty good.
Yeah?
有什么好！
All right. Let's roll!
我在途中！
你准备好大型游戏
You guys ready for the big game?
- 是的。 - 而遭太空人今天玩
Yeah.
Sam, who are the Astros playing tonight?
我不知道。
I don't know.
密尔瓦基酿酒人。 认识他们，恨他们。
The Milwaukee Brewers, all right?
梅森，你呢 这一周是怎么回事
Get to know 'em, get to hate 'em.
不错。
Mason. How you been? Huh? How was your week?
你做了什么
Pretty good.
- 没有。 - 你一直挂了乔
Yeah? What you been up to?
Not much. No?
- 是的。 - 是你最好的朋友吗
You still hanging with that kid Joe?
Yeah. And he's still your best friend?
我想是这样。
Yeah, I guess.
- 和你这一周是怎么回事 - 好吧。
Okay-
How about you? How was your week?
你做了什么
Fine.
What you been up to?
什么都不重要。
Nothing, really.
还是,,,,,,正与雕塑
You, um, still working on that sculpture project?
是的。基本完成。
Yeah. Almost finished. Yeah?
它是什么
What's it of?
别客气。
Nothing.
不，不，不，不。 所以我们不会跟我们说话。
All right, no, no, no.
No, that is not how we are going to talk to one another. All right?
我不会是那个家伙。
No, I will not be that guy. You cannot put me in that category, all right?
他们不能把我这一类。
"The biological father that l spend every other week with,
的“亲生父亲 我是谁每15天,,,
"and I make polite conversation
“我聊天谁好心,,,
"while he drives me places and buys me shit."
“当他把我拉到一边 另一个和我买的东西。 “不！
No! Talk to me.
跟我说话！ “萨曼莎，你怎么一周了”
Samantha, how was your week?
“这是困难的。分居比利和艾伦,,,
"Uh, I don't know, Dad, it was kinda tough.
“艾伦很生气，因为 他看到我说话比利,,,
"Billy and Ellen broke up, and Ellen's kinda mad at me,
“在饭厅。记住 雕塑他在做什么
"'cause she saw me talking to Billy in the cafeteria.
"And you remember that sculpture I was working on,
“这是一个独角兽的角 打破了。现在是斑马。 “
"well, it was a unicorn,
"and the horn broke off, so now it's a zebra," okay?
“但我认为它会带我像10”
"But I still think I'm gonna get an right?
“梅森，你怎么一周了 “你知道，这是相当困难的。
Mason, uh, how was your week?
"Well, Dad, you know it was kinda tough.
“乔伊是愚蠢的媒介。
"Joey's kind of a jerk, actually.
“他偷了香烟 妈妈要我抽烟。
"He stole some cigarettes from his mom and he wanted me to smoke 'em,
“我说没有，因为我知道 这将花费你离开了，爸爸。 “
"but I said no because I knew
"what a hard time you had quitting smoking, Dad."
这是怎么回事就那么难吗
How 'bout that? Is that so hard?
这些问题 很难回答。
Dad, these questions are kind of hard to answer.
什么是这么难 描述一个雕塑
What is so hard to answer about what sculpture are you making?
这是抽象！
It's abstract.
行。好的，好的。
Okay. Okay, that's good.
倪竟然不知道,,, 你感兴趣的抽象艺术。
See, I didn't know that.
I didn't know you were even interested in abstract art.
我对此不感兴趣。 í效劳。
I'm not. They make us do it.
可是，爸爸，为什么 总是我们你呢
But, Dad, why is it all on us, though?
这一周是怎么回事 谁做你走你有女朋友吗
What about you? How was your week?
Who do you hang out with?
你做了什么
Do you have a girlfriend? What have you been up to?
你说得对。
I see your point.
因此，我们必须离开 一切顺其自然，对不对
So we should just let it happen more natural, right?
这就是你说的。
That's what you're saying?
行！这就是我们要做的。
Okay, that's what we'll do.
从现在开始。
Starting now.
看看这个！
Check this out.
这是一个,,,
That would be a...
这是一只猫头鹰蝶。
That would be a Magnificent Owl. Caligo atreus.
卡利戈阿特柔斯。
- What's that one? Look at this. - Whoa!
看看这个！
What kind is that?
是什么样的呢
That looks like a Zebra Longwing. All right.
看起来像斑马长翅。
- 很好！ - 好。
Cool.
这是惊人的。
This one's incredible. That's the owl one, right?
- 这是猫头鹰吧 - 是的
Yeah. Magnificent Owl.
猫头鹰蝶。
I think he went pee-pee on you, bud.
í撒尿，朋友。
1 ,,, 2 ,,, 3 ,,, 4 ,,,
One, two, three, four, five.
5。
离我远点！
Get away from me! Get away from me!
梅森！看着我。
Yo, Mase, look at me here. Make a diamond with your hands, all right?
形成用你的双手的钻石。
Fingers and thumbs.
手指和拇指。柔软的手。
Keep your hands soft.
山姆。
Sam. Very nice.
很好。
That's how you want to catch it, just like that.
做到这一点。
Even when you're running,
仍然在运行，你仍然 思维的钻石。
that's what you're thinking about, that diamond.
金刚石和柔软的手。
That diamond and soft hands.
右。
There it is.
No,no,no.
No! Yes!
Don't let her get... No, no, no!
加油，罗杰！
Let's go, Roger!
That's it, Roger! Yeah!
当他抛出的球，他们不能沾。
Guy's incredible. He's unhittable this year.
所以，他们知道他们在看。
Now, just so you know, what we're watching here is history.
这就是历史。你看这家伙
Now, you see this guy out here?
其43年 叶率打20。
This dude is like 43 years old,
and he's striking out guys half his age.
他有安打率1,47。
This guy's ERA is 1.47, all right? Can you believe that?
你能相信吗
Now, if the Astros could just get a few runs, maybe we'd win a game.
如果太空人可以做一些 基地，我们会赢得比赛。
爸爸，你有工作吗
Dad, do you have a job?
你为什么问这个
Why would you ask me that?
妈妈想知道,,,
I don't know. Morn wanted to know,
妈妈想知道。
and I didn't know what the answer was. Morn wanted to know.
告诉妈妈,,,
All right. Well, you can tell Mom
他们只是碰巧,,,,,,我只是
that I just happen to have passed
我的第二个精算考试。
my second actuarial exam, all right?
进而,,,
So, tell her that. How's she doing?
她怎么样
Is she finishing school?
- 大学毕业 - 是所有10 ,,
Yep, all A's.
是否所有10吧
All A's, huh? Like mother, like daughter, right?
母亲去了女儿，对不对
He got that! That's out...
Oh! Oh!
Yeah! Look at that!
Yeah!
Mason! Yes!
MASON SR; Whoo!
Yeah!
- 嗨，吉米。 - 嗨，萨曼莎。
- Hey, Jimmy. - Hey, Samantha!
- 怎么样吉米 - 怎么样梅森
Hey. What's up, Jimmy?
What's going on, Mason, man?
太空人队赢了。
Astros won.
是党
You went to the game?
我是唯一一个拥有武器 没有人能带来什么
What, I'm the only one with any arms around here?
并帮助你的人吗
Nobody else can carry anything? Huh?
你在看什么
Help their old man out?
吉米，你知道是谁进来 你们这个周末。
What you watching?
Oh, come on, Jimmy, man! You knew the kids were coming this weekend.
这一次， 你能不能帮我一下
Can't you just help me out a little bit?
- 对不起，松饼。 - 不要给我松饼。
I'm sorry, muffin.
我不是他妈的狗托尼・兰德尔。
Yeah, don't "muffin" me, all right?
Don't put me in that position.
I'm not your fuckin' Tony Randall.
- 爸爸总是凌乱。 - 这不是早上。
Dad, it's always a mess.
It was not a mess this morning. Okay?
- 我砍草。 - 好。
I mowed the lawn.
Oh, yeah? Great.
来吧，让狗屎。
Oh, come on, man! Turn this shit off.
给我。
Come on, give me that thing.
- 你看比赛了吗 - 第
Did you watch the game?  No.
里赢得了 职业生涯三分球。
Lane won it with a three-run homer.
这是美丽的，对不对
It was beautiful, wasn't it?
山姆疯了。
Sam lost her mind.
他是太空人队的粉丝。
She's a huge Astros fan.
你确定。
Sure.
上周六晚月食
Saturday night was a lunar eclipse
唱了一首歌，喜欢的东西:
I sang 'em a song Went something like this
我累了睡着的孩子
Well, go to sleep, my weary babies
通过警报器
Let the sounds roll on by
今晚我们 安全是在休斯顿
Tonight we're safe here in Houston
与此摇篮曲爸爸
With this, your daddy's lullaby
她的母亲有一个新的丈夫，现在
Your mother's got a new husband now
看起来非常不错，
He seems all right
我不知道他们讲故事
I wonder if he's reading them stories
如果你给他们一个吻晚安
And kissing them good night
他们说，他们想念我
Well, babysitters say they miss me
应该不希望这是真的
I know I shouldn't hope it's true
老师说我的孩子 绘制一个家庭的照片
Teacher says my son paints pictures of a family
所有的蓝色。
All in blue
他说，他很惊讶 窃窃私语的窗口:
She says she caught him whispering to the window
“爸爸，快回来吧”
Will Daddy please come home?
我知道我可以打电话
I know I could call him up
但如果母亲需要调用
But what if his mother answers the phone?
- 你有没有刷牙 - 什么
You brush your teeth? What?
你有没有刷牙
Did you brush your teeth?
是的。
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
难道你不保持睡眠 这些斗牛场的职位
You gonna fall asleep with those things in your head?
也许吧。
Maybe.
尽量不要。
Yeah, well, try not to, all right? Okay.
- 我关掉灯 - 是的。
Want me to turn off the light? Okay. Sure.
- 晚安，山姆。 - 晚安，爸爸。
Good night, Sam. Night, Dad.
- 晚安，山姆。 - 晚安，吉米。
Good night, Jimmy.
- 今天很有趣，不是吗 - 是的，它是。对不起。
Hey. That was a fun day, right?
Yeah, it was. Sorry.
- 什么 - 这已是梅森。
Why? That Mason had to be there, you know.
- 晚安。 - 晚安。
Good night. Good night.
爸爸
Dad?
在现实中有,,,
There's no, like, real magic in the world, right?
神奇的世界，不是吗
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
你知道，像,,,,,,精灵之类的东西。
You know, like elves and stuff.
人们发明了。
People just made that up.
我不知道。
Oh, I don't know.
是什么让你认为 神奇的精灵类似,,,
I mean, what makes you think that elves are any more magical
像一条鲸鱼。
than something like a whale?
你了解我吗
You know what I mean? What if I told you a story about
如果我告诉你如何,,,
how underneath the ocean,
下洋有这,,,
there was this giant sea mammal
使用巨型哺乳动物 声纳和唱歌
that used sonar and sang songs
什么是如此之大，他的心脏 是车的大小，可以,,,
and it was so big that its heart was the size of a car
通过你的血管爬行
and you could crawl through the arteries?
你看起来很神奇吧
I mean, you'd think that was pretty magical, right?
是的。
Yeah.
但是,,,说,,, 在这个非常时刻，
But, like, right this second,
世界上没有任何精灵，对吧
there's, like, no elves in the world, right?
第一句话，没有精灵。
No. Technically, no elves.
很好，伙计们。
Love you, guys. All right. Be well. See you, Dad.
有一个伟大的一周。
Have a great week. Sam, I'll see you next weekend?
- 山姆，看你这个周末。 - 是的。对了，我忘了。
All right. Oh, yeah, that's right. What?
Cindy的生日上周六。
Suzy has a birthday party next Saturday.
- 你睡着了吗 - 是的。
A sleepover? Yeah.
我会跟你妈妈。
All right. I'll talk to your mom about it.
不用担心。玩的很开心。
Bye,Dad. Don't worry about it, okay?
Have a great week. Okay. Had a great time.
你怎么不知道如何做到这一点
Oh, man.
How do you guys not know how to do this?
我会尽快标记。
I'll make you some bookmarks. Just a second. Pictures...
Ooh. She looks nice.
兰迪・梅森，爸爸想了。
Randy, Mason, Dad wants you guys downstairs.
- 为了什么 - 理发。
Why? You're getting haircuts.
它看起来好多了。
This is gonna look so much better.
你看起来像个男人，而不是一个小女孩。
You're gonna look like a man, instead of like a little girl.
眉毛太吧拜伦
You're taking the eyebrows off next, right, Byron?
梅森，我们要走了。
Mason, we're leaving.
你是不是有病！
You're not sick.
- 再见，伙计们。 - 再见了，妈妈。
- Bye, guys. - Bye, Mom.
和梅森
Where's Mason?
这感觉并不好。 我不会去上学。
He doesn't feel too good. I don't think he's going to school.
病人一样。
He's totally faking it.
雅。
Bye.
梅森，会发生什么
Mason, what's going on?
我不舒服。
I don't feel good.
你的头是好的， 所以下床。
Yeah, well, your head feels fine.
我服用。 你有五分钟。不要迟到。
So get your ass out of bed.
I'm gonna drive you to school.
You got five minutes, and don't make me late.
无论是问我！
I mean, he didn't even ask! He just cut it.
他切割，准备好了。
It's my hair!
是我的头发！
Well, no wonder you were angry. I'd be angry, too.
难怪你生气。 我会了。
我是火星人吧。
I look like a Martian now.
亲爱的，我会跟他谈 后来，好吗
Honey, you know what? I'm gonna talk to him about it later. Okay?
你应该叫 但他的手机。
Yeah, I tried to call you, but you didn't answer your phone.
对不起。
I'm so sorry. I've been so busy with school.
我一直这样 忙碌的大学,,,
如果有帮助，它只是发 并会再长出来。
For what it's worth, it's hair and it will grow back.
现在我可以看到你的 漂亮的眼睛和你的脸狐狸。
And now I can see your pretty eyes and your foxy face.
而你为什么要结婚 跟他在一起这是一个总的白痴。
Why did you even marry him?
He's such a jerk!
比尔有好东西。 没有人是完美的。
Well, Bill has his good qualities.
You know, nobody's perfect. And now we have a family.
现在我们有一个家庭。
We already had a family.
我们已经有了一个家庭。
“我宣誓效忠的标志 美国，
I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America...
“而到了民国 由其所持有，
...and to the Republic for which it stands,
“上帝之下的一个国家，不可分割，
one nation, under God,
“自由与正义。”
indivisible, with liberty and justice for all.
背诵德州的誓言。
Please join me in the Texas Pledge.
“荣誉德州标志;
Honor the Texas flag.
“我宣誓效忠，德州，
I pledge allegiance to thee,
“一个上帝之下的状态， 一个不可分割的整体。 “
Texas one and indivisible.
谢谢。有一个座位。
Thank you. You may be seated.
雅！
All right.
如你所知，我们是 与神话中的工作，
All right, class, as you know,
we've been working on our mythology projects,
并写神和女神。
and you're going to be writing papers about gods and goddesses.
我们列出了 众神在黑板上。
We've listed those gods and goddesses here on the board.
有一对夫妇 怪物对于那些有兴趣。
We added a couple of monsters
for some of you who might be interested in that.
他们会写一篇文章 关于神和女神。
And you're going to write your essay about your god and goddess,
要解决所有的问题，
and to make sure that you cover everything,
确保你做这些事情。
let's make sure that we do all of these things right here.
首先，我们必须 命名为神或女神。
First of all, you need to name your god or goddess,
而且你要添加的“谁”，“什么”,,,,,,
and you need to include who, what, when, where, why and how.
梅森，你的头发，我喜欢它！
“当”，“哪里”，“为什么”和“怎么样”。
So make sure that you cover all those things
验证它是 所有写杂文。
when you're writing your essay.
驴。
There's a bump right there.
- 再见。 - 是的。
I'll see you later, guys.
Yeah.
- 妈妈，你还好吗 - 发生了什么事
- Mom, are you okay? - What happened?
不，不。去的房子。 一套房子。去的房子！
No.
Go in the house! Go! Go in the house! Go in the house!
你的母亲出了车祸。
Your mother had a little accident.
现在它的滥情
Now she's being dramatic.
下车他妈的 地板，奥利维亚。神。
Get off the fucking floor, Olivia. For Christ's sake!
我带你去喝一杯我的晚餐。
I'm having a drink with my dinner.
任何人有问题吗
Anybody else have a problem with that?
- 萨曼莎 - 第
Hmm?
Samantha? No.
- 柯以敏 - 第
Mindy?
No.
我以为不是。
I didn't think So.
我不喜欢我的非常多，你，梅森
You don't like me much, do you, Mason?
我不喜欢我非常喜欢。
That's okay. I don't like me either.
你认为这很有趣
You think that's funny? Huh?
你认为这是有趣的
You think that's fuckin' funny?
怎么了你是否感到被排除在外
What's the matter, you feeling a little left out?
清洁它，该死！它清理干净！
Clean it up, God damn it! Clean it up.
清洁它怎么就！我讨厌的南瓜！
Bill! Clean it up, God damn it!
I hate squash!
女孩，我会付。我有三个 工作现在,,,
Pearl.
I'm gonna pay you.
你有多少次看到它，梅森
I'm working three jobs right now.
How many times can you watch that, Mason?
这是有趣的。
It's funny. I'm driving a cab.
我现在和我的朋友。 回顾我的C,V,
I'm inside with my buddy right now just going over my résumé.
我会坚持
Okay, you know what? You need to relax.
你知道吗你需要冷静下来。
我要我的钱！
Look, why do you need your money so fast? Come on.
为什么需要快
已经错了
- Has he ever gotten this bad before? - No.
没有，但我哭了很多次。
But he's yelled a lot.
但投掷和摔东西。
Yeah, but he hasn't thrown and broken stuff.
是的。你是喝醉了。我就知道。 你喝醉了。
Yeah. You're drunk. I knew it.
You're already drunk.
它们的细胞。
Give me your cell phones.
所以没有人提及她。
So nobody talked to her, huh?
- 梅森 - 第
Mason?
No.
- 柯以敏 - 第
Mindy? No.
我相信你。
I believe you.
- 萨曼莎 - 第
Samantha?
No.
我没有跟她说话。他离开的消息。
I didn't talk to her. She left a message.
什么好说的
What'd she say?
不多。
Nothing much.
什么好说的
What did she say?
以后会回来。
She said she'd be back later.
是这样吗 “难道我会回来后，”点击
And that's all, "I'll be back later," click?
他说，“留在 季过来。 “
She said, "Stay in your rooms. I'll be back later."
回答是 在自己的房间。仅此而已。
I'll be back later, stay in your rooms. And that's all? Hmm?
是的。
Yeah.
在哪里
Where is she?
- 我不知道。 - 他在哪里
I don't know. Where is she?
说没有！
She didn't say!
所有的汽车。
All right. Everybody, get in the car.
快！车！
Hurry up! Get in the car!
删除您的收据
资金不足
- 仍然没有工作。 - 妈的。
It's still not working.
WELBROCK Oh, bullshit.
它夺走了一切。
She took it all.
兰迪，去收集。
All right, Randy, go cash this.
告诉他我不舒服什么的。
Tell them I'm not feeling well or something. I don't know.
梅森，陪它！
Mason, go with him.
以我的身份。
Here. There's my ID.
晚上好，伙计。 我怎样才能帮助
Hi, good afternoon, fellas. What can I do for you today?
这是什么
Now what's this?
Can't read this.
这不是你！
Hey!
是谁
This isn't you! Who is this?
这是我们的,,,,,,父亲。
It's our dad.
这感觉并不好。
He's not feeling well.
是的！我知道。
Oh! Hey! Yeah, I know him. Okay, here we go.
让我们来看看。
五百元。
Five hundred bucks.
One, two, three, four...
五百元。
Five hundred bucks. All right?
不要忘了鉴定。
Don't forget your dad's ID.
把你的父亲，儿子的照顾。你只有一个。
Now take care of your dad now, son. You only got the one.
他妈的！
WELBROCK Damn it.
闪开！天啊！
Get outta the way. Jesus Christ.
God...
Calm down!
萨曼莎！
Samantha! Mason!
梅森！
萨曼莎！
Samantha!
凡他妈的去了
Where the hell have you been?
我离开你，比尔。我们离开这里。
I'm leaving you, Bill. We're moving out.
我对此表示怀疑。
I doubt that.
萨曼莎，梅森！低！
Samantha, Mason! Come down!
我不认为。
No, mmm-mmm, don't think so. Oh, who's this?
- 这一个 - 我不是在这里为您服务！
- I'm not here for you! - Oh, really?
我知道。你在这里保护 我的妻子。谢谢。
Oh, I know, you're here to protect my wife from me.
回来了！
Well, thank you so much, you two. Okay, stay back!
你为什么不来
Why don't you come inside here? Huh? Come inside here.
请登录。真是见鬼，你在做什么
Where the hell are you going?
重新站起来。他们不会去任何地方。
Get your ass upstairs! You're not going anywhere.
够了！来吧！
Stop! Come on!
在那里他们觉得他们是谁
Where the hell do you think you're going? Get upstairs!
- 没有人去任何地方，该死。 - 够了！
What the hell... Nobody's going anywhere, God damn it!
- 不，他妈的,,, - 不要碰我的孩子！
No, God damn it! Stop it.
- 好。带他们。 - 请勿触摸！
Don't touch my kids!
All right, take 'em. Go on, go on.
- 上车！ - 以他们！带他们！
- Don't touch them! - Take 'em.
Take 'em then, just take 'em! Get in the car.
阿德兰特！
Go!
进来！
Get upstairs! Olivia!
奥利维亚！
Seat belts! Put your seat belts on.
将自己带。
我们要去哪里
Where are we going?
我们将留在卡罗尔一段时间。
We're going to stay with Carol and her family for a while.
不回头！
Don't look back.
一切都会好起来的。
It's gonna be okay.
And we see that
We're all in this together
And it shows When we stand hand in hand
李和梅森。以 休息一下。这里的三明治。
Hey, Lee and Mason. Guys, when you want
to take a break, here's a snack.
...going on...
Wildcats in the house Everybody say it loud
Wildcats everywhere
Wave your hands up in the air
嘿，艾比。
Abby, why don't you come and help me with this?
我可以帮忙吗
Why couldn't Randy and Mindy come with us?
为什么不来兰迪和柯以敏
我不是他的法定监护人，我的爱。 这将是一个绑架。我不能,,,
I'm not their legal guardian, honey.
That would be kidnapping. I can't just...
会发生什么事
What's gonna happen to them?
导师的时候，会发生什么 是危险的，辱骂性的法律
What happens when their legal guardian is dangerous and abusive?
我不知道，亲爱的。
I don't know, honey.
我打电话给他的妈妈。我打了电话 保护机构。
I called their mom. I called the Child Protective Services.
在这里，我中有你和你的兄弟。
I have you and your brother.
我们是在一个情况 危险的。这是我的责任。
We are in a dangerous situation.
You're my responsibility.
会回来看
Are we ever gonna see them again?
我不知道。
I don't know.
我希望如此。
I hope so.
多久，我们会在这里
How much longer are we gonna be here?
不多。我们是,,,
Not long. We're...
I don't...
我没有答案的一切！
I don't know. I don't have the answer, baby.
嘿嘿。我们很高兴 只要他们想要他们。
Listen.
We are happy to have you here as long as you want.
所需的时间。
As long as you need.
这很有趣，不是吗
This is fun for us, isn't it? Mmm-hmm.
就像有一个姐姐。 就像有一个哥哥。
Yeah, it's like having a big sister?
我们将帮助都没有。 也不会注意到我们的存在。
Like having a brother.
We're gonna help out, right?
You're not even gonna know we're here.
Okay.
妈妈，太可怕了！
Mom, this is awful.
你离开我在停车场 学校。不知道的人。
You're dumping me in some parking lot of this school
where I don't even know anyone!
我把我所有的朋友 我什至不能说再见。
I'm leaving all my friends, and I didn't even get to say goodbye!
不知道哪里去了！
I don't know where to go!
萨曼莎，只是 通过那扇门。
Samantha, you go right through that door.
该办公室是存在的。
The office is right there. They're expecting you.
恭候您的光临。他们会给你你的日程安排。 在这里，你去吃饭了。
They're gonna give you your schedule.
我会在这里找到你在第3和30。
Here's your lunch money.
I will pick you up right here at 3:30.
我和脏衣服，因为,,,
I'm wearing dirty clothes because you wouldn't even let us get our stuff!
不让我们走 发现我们的东西！
We don't even have a place to live!
也没有住的地方！
This sucks!
太臭！
Samantha, I'm doing the best I can!
萨曼莎！
我尽我所能！
And you're right, it sucks!
而你说的没错，它吮吸！
But it doesn't suck half as much as having a drunk fool
但不臭一半 有什么白痴喝醉吸,,,
敲打你的头撞墙！
slam your head against a wall!
所以足够的态度 狗屎！表带自己。
So cut your horseshit attitude!
Put your seat belt on!
如果你需要什么，我会在课堂上112。
You know, if you need anything, I'm in Room 112, right?
这是太,,美的课堂。
Okay-
This is Mrs. Darby's room.
一切都会好起来的，亲爱的。
Oh, honey, it's gonna be okay.
妈妈！
Mom.
您有责任 你自己的行为！
Dude, did you see that?
That concert was awful.
Hook, I mean, when he smashed that board against that microphone...
您梅森
Are you Mason? Yeah.
我是达比太太。 很高兴认识你。
Hi, I'm Mrs. Darby. I'm glad to meet you.
坐在这里。
Why don't you sit here?
- 肯尼。 - 是的，夫人。
Kenny! Off.
肯尼，这是梅森 我要你今天表现的地方。
Yes, ma'am.
Kenny, this is Mason,
and I want you to show him around today,okay?
Got it.
你好。欢迎您到一塌糊涂。
Hey, dude. Welcome to the suck.
类！听着！
Everybody, listen up!
我们有一个新的学生和我们在一起。
We have a new student joining us today.
他的名字叫梅森。 这是坐在后排。
His name is Mason, he's sitting in the back row.
肯尼将成为你的好友，但是,,,
Kenny's going to be his buddy, but I want each one of you
希望每个人都拿 时间到今天现身
to take the time today to introduce yourselves
欢迎到学校。
and welcome him to school. Okay?
是不是好开始。
All right? Let's get started.
你想要什么
What?
我们可以把 在你的花园里，奥巴马的海报
Oh, hi.
我看起来支持 巴拉克・侯赛因・奥巴马
Can I put an Obama sign in your yard?
Do I look like a Barack Hussein Obama supporter?
号
No.
这是私人财产，离开。
This is private property. Get off.
你可以拍！
I could shoot you!
- 真是个白痴。 - 有一个南方旗在家里。
What a dick.
He had a Confederate flag on his house.
我喜欢它。年轻人 工作支持奥巴马。有什么好！
I love it.
Young Obama supporters out on the trail, this is great!
你有没有通过学校来吗
Are you doing this through your school?
我的爸爸是一个大风扇。
Um, our dad's a big supporter.
有什么好。我们必须 合赢。
Oh, that's great.
I mean, we have just got to pull together to get this win, right?
是的。
Yeah.
我想这两个！
Ah, I just love him so much!
我做了一个梦，梦见她吻。 他是那么帅吧
I have these dreams where I'm just kissing him,
'cause I just love him so much!
He's so cute, isn't he?
我做了一些衬衫 我的孩子，“我妈妈支持奥巴马。”
Yeah.
You know, I made these T-shirts for my kids.
"My Mama's For Obama."
- 你喜欢它 - 是的。 - 这是很好的，对吗
Do you like it? Yeah.
- It's good, right? -  Yeah.
感谢您的海报！
- Thanks for the sign! - No problem.
很好！看起来不错！
All right! Looks good!
有多少人吗两个 我们走吧。来吧，萨姆。
How many you got left, two?
All right, all right, we're done. Let's get out of here.
- 去海报麦凯恩。 - 什么
Come on, Sam.
麦凯恩海报。
Go get that McCain sign, would you?
杀青了！来吧。
What? Get the McCain sign. Go rip it up, come on.
把它！是的，是的，是的！
Get it, get it, get it, 90.90,90!
好工作。
Good job, good job. Proud of you, son.
我为你感到骄傲。
他们要逮捕你你。
You guys are gonna get us arrested.
我是一个爱国主义者。 有时你必须在生活中战斗。
Look, I'm a patriot, all right?
And sometimes in this life you gotta fight.
那你在这些政党做什么
And what is it that you do at these parties?
我不知道,,,,,,我说话，跳舞，听音乐。
I don't know. Talk, dance, listen to music.
这有什么比去更有趣 í阵营你哥哥和你的父亲吗
Uh-huh. And that's more fun to you than going camping
with your brother and your father who love you.
是的。
Yes. Sorry.
对不起！
Wow. ls there gonna be alcohol there?
会不会有酒精
Probably not.
我不这么认为。或许有些 的大个子。
- Maybe some of the seniors. Mmm-hmm.
我知道党是什么。
I know what this party is.
父母外出 有人得了啤酒小桶，
The parents are out of town, right?
将是巨大的乐趣; 他们将摧毁整个房子。
Somebody's scored a keg, right?
You guys are gonna have a good time, trash the whole house.
- 无 - 不，爸爸。 Amy是非常负责任的。
Right? Am I right? No.
No, Dad. Amy's really responsible.
Mmm-hmm.
谁将会在那里
Who's gonna be there?
莫林，恭，艾米,,,大家好！
Marie, Christine, Amy. Everyone.
请问家伙 在你的Facebook页面
Is that guy on your Facebook page, is he gonna be there?
谁
Who?
这是拥抱你 并有头发遮住眼睛。
Come on, the guy that's got his arm wrapped around you,
- 加勒特 - 加勒特所以它叫什么名字
with his hair over his eyes.
Garret?
Garret. Is that his name? All right.
将加勒特在那里
Is Garret gonna be there?
- 这是可能的。 - 可能的,,,
Probably.
我学更多的从她的 在他的Facebook页面,,,
Probably. Uh-huh. You see?
I learn more about her from her Facebook page
他闪闪发光的谈话。
than I do from our scintillating conversation.
是你的男朋友吗
Is he your boyfriend?
类似的东西。
Kind of.
你认识他吗你一直在房子里
Have you met him? Has he been around the house?
有时。
Sometimes.
vece中的“s”吗
Sometimes? Zzz?
你有男朋友吗！
You have a boyfriend!
Wow.
- 听说过佩林的 - 是的。
Have you heard of Sarah Palin?
什么保险 你知道你17岁的女儿吗
Yes.
What's the one thing you know about
Sarah Palin's 17-year-old daughter?
- 什么是怀孕了吗 - 这是正确的。
She's pregnant? That's right.
并且它是什么，你不会知道,,,
And what is the one thing that you are not going to be
在两年内，刚满17岁
in a couple of years when you turn 17?
- 怀孕吗 - 没错。
Pregnant? That's right!
什么是两 如何实现这一目标
All right, now, what are the two ways
第一个,,,,,,没有 关系好不好这是第一个。
that you can achieve that goal?
First is
not have any sex, okay?
不要,,,,,,这并不工作 还有你的母亲和我。
That's the first way, okay? Just not engage in that.
That did not work out very well for your mother and me.
什么是第二
And what's the second way?
- 你要去哪里 - 洗手间。
Where you going? Bathroom.
没有必要去洗手间。 坐，梅森。
You don't have to go to the bathroom.
Sit down, Mason, just sit down.
什么是第二种形式
What's the second way?
她的母亲并没有说过他们谈这个
Huh?
Has your mother talked to you guys about this stuff?
- 爸爸。 - 不，伤势严重。 你刚才讲,,,
No,Dad!
No, come on, has she talked to you about
避孕药
contraception?
什么你有没有,,,,,, 避孕套，你教训他们一下吗
Huh?
What, has she... Condoms?
- 爸爸，请。 - 什么
She talked about that? No, Dad, please, stop.
- 别闹了，请。 - 加勒特有,,,,,,
What?
- 天啊！ - 什么
Does Garret have a condom? Oh, God!
山姆，我们需要谈论这个。
Dad!  What? Come on.
Sam, we have to be able to talk about this, all right?
来吧，我们可以。
Come on, we do. We can do it, we can do it.
刚听我说完好吗 这是如此艰难，我和你。
Just stay with me here, all right?
说真的，我看过一篇文章 在报纸的一天，
It's as hard for me as it is for you. But seriously, all right?
I read an article in the paper the other day that said
他说，虽然青少年 美国是不是性活跃
that although US teenagers are not the most sexually active,
有平等的速率 最高怀孕。
we have the highest rate of teenage pregnancy, okay?
你好。
Hey-
- 陈怡蓉，你怎么样 - 很高兴见到你。
Oh, hey, Tammy, how you doing? What's going on?
是啊，我也是。
Nice to see you.
陈怡蓉，这是我的女儿萨曼莎。 而这个儿子梅森。
Oh, yeah, good to see you. Yeah.
Um, Tammy, this is my daughter Samantha. Hey.
And this is, uh, Mason Junior right here.
- 萨卢达。 - 嗨。
- Mason Junior. - Tammy.
你好，梅森。恩坎塔达。
Say hi. Hi.
我听说过你。
Hi, Mason, nice to meet you. Heard a lot about you guys.
- 你在这里做什么 - 我的朋友。
What're you doing here?
I'm just here with some friends.
和你在做什么
Oh, wow. Yeah.
我们将营地。
What are you guys up to?
虽然她不会去 营。你去参加一个聚会。
Um, we're going camping.
Well, no, this one is not going camping.
This one is going to a party.
- 有趣。 - 我们的人，营地。
Oh, fun.
男性阵营。很好。
But we, the men, are going camping.
The boys are going camping.
All right, very nice.
是明天
Well, uh, we still on for tomorrow? Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
是啊。离开7，我会打电话给你。
No, I'll drop him off at 7:00 and then I'll just call you.
好吧。我也很高兴 满足你们俩。再见。
Okay. Right?
Great. It was really nice meeting you both.
- 再见。 - 再见。
Take care.
Talk to you soon. Bye. I'll see you. I'll see you.
不要像她那样。
Don't look at me like that, all right?
好了，结束吧。
Look, just to finish the point, okay?
我23岁的时候你出生。 涂妈妈Tambien。
I was 23 when your mom had you, all right? So was she.
我们没有放在最好的 情况是伟大的父母。
All right, and we didn't put ourselves
in the best position to be great parents.
我会是一个好父亲,,,,,, 你们两个，你知道吗
And I wish that...
I wish I were a better parent to you guys, all right?
我希望你能 从我的错误中吸取教训。
And I hope that you can learn from my mistakes, okay?
即使用了安全套。
All right. So wear a condom, okay? Oh!
或,,,加勒特,,,等等。
Or get Garret to...
I don't know, whatever.
听这首歌。
Listen to this song, all right?
我想忙
I try to stay busy
传统的歌词和“国家” 传统的老学校。
Just straight-up... The lyrics in this,
我洗洗碗，短草
straight-up old-school country song.
I do the dishes I mow the lawn
听产品的质量。 这就像,,,,,,“艾比路”
Listen to the production of this.
Production's like Abbey Road or something.
尽可能保持忙碌
虽然我知道你永远不会
Even though I know You're not coming home
你知道，女人离开了。传统。
You know, his old woman's gone.
酷。
Straight-up. Nothing fancy.
我尽量保持屋内整洁
I try to keep the house nice and neat
我把我的床，换床单
Make my bed I change the sheets
直到我学会了用洗衣机
I even learned how to use the washing machine
拥有一切的清洁并不能改变什么
Keeping things clean Doesn't change anything
我想，我有你的专业知识。
Yeah, I think she's about to get her master's degree.
你会寻求教学工作
Well, then she's gonna start applying for teaching jobs?
我认为他做了什么。
I think she already has.
是吗在哪里
Really? Where?
- 无处不在。 - 为什么所有的德州
All over.
- 是 - 。如果你有移动 你必须移动。这没什么大不了的。
All over Texas? Yeah.
Well, if you gotta move, you gotta move, you know? It's no big deal.
我们会处理。
We can handle that. I'll still come get you every other weekend.
我会继续下去，每两个星期。
I mean, unless she moves 500 miles away or something,
如果你在800千米左右移动 驱动器必须是更长的时间。
it'll just be a little bit more car time.
这是没有问题的。
No big deal.
- 我生病移动。 - 当然。
I'm just kind of sick of moving.
但你永远不知道。 也许我得动。
Well, I bet you are.
But, you know, you never know.
我的工作，以 一家保险公司。
I might have to move. Right?
I'm working for this insurance company now.
这些公司 购买和出售所有的时间。
These places get bought and sold all the time.
我们必须接受它。
You know, we'll just roll with it.
我以为你是一个音乐家。
I thought you were a musician.
我，但是,,,,,,生活是昂贵的，你知道的。
I am,
but life is expensive, you know?
你要负责。
Guy's got to be responsible.
你有什么感想
What do you think?
Hey! Hey!
嘿，你！什么是不尊重！
Oh. you!
Punk kid! You got no respect!
而在保龄球馆的红发
You know that redhead at the bowling alley?
是啊，这是怎么回事
Sure. What about her?
- 你认识她吗 - 我们已经见过几次。
Do you know her well?
Uh, you know, we've hung out a little bit.
是你的女朋友吗
Is she your girlfriend?
你是什么意思
How do you mean?
嗯,,,,,,你吻
Like, have you kissed her?
Um...
是的。是啊，我已经吻了。
Yeah. Yeah, I've kissed her.
和你你有女朋友吗
What about you? Have you got a girlfriend?
类似的东西。
Sort of.
真的吗
Really?
你,,,,,,吻
Have you, uh, kissed her?
号
Not really.
做了什么
Yeah? What have you done?
- 在电话交谈。 - 清除。
Well, we talked on the phone.
- 怎么样 - 非常糟糕。
0h. yeah!
How did that go?
Pretty terrible.
为什么呢
Why?
在学校里，我们可以 谈很多事情，但,,,
Well, when we're at school, we got plenty to talk about,
手机似乎 我们没有任何共同之处。
but when we're alone or on the phone,
it's like we have nothing in common.
什么
Nothing?
不感兴趣的音乐 和电子游戏,,,,,,
She's not interested in music or video games or...
夏天的三个最佳影片。
Three best movies this summer. Right.
黑暗骑士一战 电影和菠萝快车
Tropic Thunder, Dark Knight and Pineapple Express.
- 那又怎样 - 它说，所有的臭！
Yeah, what about 'em? She said they all sucked.
你对什么感兴趣
Okay, what's she interested in?
我不知道。去市区 与他们的女朋友傻购物。
I don't know.
Going to the mall with her stupid friends?
- 是她漂亮吗小心那里。 - 是的。
Well, is she cute? Watch your step there.
Yeah. Yeah? All right.
做到以下几点。
Well, here's what you do, all right?
首先，你做了很多的问题。
First off, you gotta ask her a lot of questions.
然后，你要听 反应。证明对她的兴趣。
Then you have to listen to the answers, all right?
Actually be interested in her, all right?
如果你能做到，你会 光年领先于他人。
If you can do those things,
you're gonna be light years ahead of all the other guys.
这是最好的梅伦格 软烤了我的生活。
Okay. This is the best s'more I ever made in my life, all right?
这是真棒。我看它。
This is absolute peak. Look at this. Yeah. Yeah.
浅棕色，无烧伤,,,
Honey brown, no burn.
还有什么比在商店出售。
Look at that, huh?
Sell that in the store. Mmm.
值得一商业。
That's like advertisement worthy. Mmm-hmm.
- 沃西的广告。 - 是的。
Advertisement quality.
Yeah.
你认为它会采取另一种 星球大战
Mmm.
You think they ever will make another Star Wars?
我不知道。如果他们做了另一个,,,
I don't know. I think if they were gonna make another one,
应该在游戏期间。
that the period where this game is set
- 接下来是什么。 - 是的。
is where it would have to be,
'cause there's nothing after, really.
- 绝地归来的结束了。 - 没有什么事情可做。
Yeah. No, Return of the Jedi, it's over. There's nothing...
您可以将 汉斯只有西斯领主。
Yeah, there's nothing else to do there.
You gonna turn Han Solo into a Sith Lord?
Yeah. What are you gonna do? Right.
如果我能离开这个高速公路
没有我杀死或捕获
我将走在这条道路 在一团烟雾
以土地 曾经，我也从来没买过
- 美好的一天。 - 好。
Good morning. Morning.
- 你要不要上厕所 - 是的。
You gotta pee?
瞄准射击。
Sure. Mmm-hmm.
自定义,,,旧机。
Hit the campfire.
Ancient Native American custom.
给什么了地上。
You're gonna give back to the Earth what you take from it,
虽然不是森林火灾风险。
and you don't burn the forest down.
好。玩的很开心。
Okay, guys, have a good day!
梅森，不要忘记。我有一个类 今天晚些时候。山姆，你会发现。
Mason, don't forget, I have to teach late today.
- 是的，山姆 - 是的。
Sam's gonna pick you up. Right, Sam? Yeah.
- 再见！ - 再见。
All right. Okay. Bye, guys.
See you.
你好。
Hey.
这就是你得到了什么
That's what I was talking to you about.
祝你好运。
Yeah. Good luck with that.
See you, man.
- 不要逼我！ Putita。 - 我没有。
Don't bump into me! Little bitch!
你是说我说谎
I didn't!
号
You calling me a liar?
不作恶，混蛋。
No.
Don't act like you're tough shit, motherfucker.
看来宝宝 可爱的不是很好。
I don't think pretty boy's hair's good enough.
不要碰我，柴草！
Don't touch me, faggot!
你是个混蛋。
You're a fuckin' asshole.
您好，梅森！
Hey, Mason!
嗨，吉尔。
MASON'. Hey, Jill.
你要去哪里
So, where're you going?
上大学。
Over to the college.
会发生什么呢
What's going on there?
- 我妈妈教导。 - 好。
My mom's a teacher.
- 这是什么教 - 心理学，我想。
Oh, cool. What does she teach?
Psychology, I think.
你是做什么
What're you up to?
我妈妈拥有Neilworks。 是艺术家和工匠。
Oh, my mom owns Needleworks.
所以我走来走去。
The arts and crafts store over there.
我得去医院很快。
So I'm just kinda hangin' out.
But I'm supposed to be going to the hospital soon.
为什么呢
How come?
你知不知道考特尼
You know Courtney?
染了头发的女孩 黑色和鼻环
Girl with the dyed black hair and the nose ring?
使用挂脖永远,,,
Wears Hot Topic every day?
我想是这样。
I think so.
我们是最好的朋友， 但我们已经疏远。
We used to be best friends growing up,
but we've kind of grown apart.
他变得非常情绪， 我相信很势利，但,,,
She sorta got all emo, she thinks I'm a prep,
仍然认为你是我的朋友。
but I still consider her a friend.
嗯，她把他的手腕之一。
Anyway, she cut one of her wrists.
我不知道严重性， 但我觉得我应该去。
I don't know how bad, but I think I should go visit.
你在看什么
So what're you reading?
“冠军早餐”的 库尔特・冯内古特。
Uh, it's Breakfast of Champions. Kurt Vonnegut.
我觉得他喜欢我的大哥哥。
I think my older brother likes him.
我读 “杀死一只知更鸟”，为第三次。
I'm reading To Kill a Mockingbird for the third time.
我的朋友取笑我。
My friends make fun of me.
我一定要在学校里唯一的女孩 没看过暮光之城的书。
I think I'm the only girl in the whole school
who doesn't like the Twilight books.
- 你读 - 当然不是。
Have you read 'em?
我想,,,,,,但这么俗气！
Sure haven't.
I tried,
but it was so cheesy!
如何圣马科斯
So, how do you like San Marcos?
没关系。
I like it all right.
它是非常小 休斯顿，但也不坏。
It's a lot smaller than Houston, but it seems pretty cool.
- 你一直住在这里 - 是的。
Have you always lived here?
如果你在这里想要一个大的城市， 你必须去圣安东尼奥和奥斯汀。
Yeah.
If you want the big city around here,
you have to drive to San Antonio or Austin.
你知道吗
Have you been there yet?
我去圣安东尼奥 这一天，但不是奥斯汀。
I went to San Antonio for a day,
but I haven't been to Austin yet.
这是那里的大孩子去了。
That's where all the high school kids go
周末音乐会之类的东西。
on weekends for shows and stuff.
所以我一直在说。
That's what I've heard.
你会党 肖纳下周末
So, are you going to Shauna's party next weekend?
这是我听说过，但我不知道。
Um, I think I heard about it. I'm not really sure, though.
- 你应该。 - 为什么
Well, you should!
娜娜你疯狂 我知道他想要你。
Why's that?
Well, LeeAnne has a big crush on you,
and I know she was hoping you would go.
没有女朋友，对不对
You don't have a girlfriend, do you?
没有的时候。
Not currently.
那么，你一定要来。
Well then, you should come.
- 我会先打电话了 确保您。 - 行。
I'll tell Chase to make sure you're there.
不要告诉娜娜 我说。这会杀了我。
Okay-
But don't tell LeeAnne I told you that. She'd kill me.
我不会。
I won't.
- 我得走了。再见。 - 再见。
Well, I better get going.
See you later. Bye.
他们的认知系列。 他采访了孤儿。
His cognitive theories, his interviews with orphans,
他的工作行为学。
ethology theorists' work,
然后他又 被支持的,,,
and then he in turn
was supported strongly by Harry Harlow's rhesus monkey study.
研究 恒河猴哈利哈洛。
Now, you guys, you gotta think,
认为这是十年 1950这是一些过激！
this is the 1950s, this was radical!
这个矛盾 学习的经典理论,,,
This flew in the face of traditional learning theory,
空调 B,F,经典斯金纳。
of B.F. Skinner's classical and instrumental conditioning.
鲍尔比认为,,,
Now, Bowlby's gonna argue that
人类生存 取决于我们坠入爱河。
human survival depends on us falling in love.
取决于谁我爱我的妈妈。
It depends on me falling in love with my mother
而我的母亲是爱我的。
and my mother falling in love with me.
如果没有，
And if that doesn't happen,
我们注定。
we're pretty much doomed.
想想吧。一只老虎跑 我们的族人穿越山洞。
Now think about it.
A tiger chases her tribe out of a cave
一个理想的母亲 “我的孩子！我爱你！”会保护你的！“
Now, an ideal mother goes,
"My baby! I love you, I'll protect you!"
或“你呢为了什么我会 要帮忙吗 íentorpecerás你。 “
Or, "Well, you, why am I gonna pick you up? You're gonna slow me down.
“你,,,,,,老虎的食物。”
"You are tiger kibble!"
下周我们将讨论 对鲍尔比的依恋的四个阶段。
So, next week, we are gonna get into
Bowlby's four stages of attachment.
你们当中有些人 有类艾琳娜。
Oh, oh... Uh, Professor Douglas and I...
我和她将举办 会议在我家。
Some of you might have classes with Elena.
She and I are hosting a little pre-Thanksgiving get-together at my place,
谁要来，欢迎。
so if anyone wants to come, please stop by.
我不是一个伟大的厨师。
I'm not the greatest cook.
Thanks.
萨曼莎！
Samantha!
凭啥 你是不是你的兄弟吗
Why the hell didn't you pick up your brother like you said you would?
我知道你会说,,,
Okay. Mom... Morn, I know what you're gonna say.
她迟到了 我们不能回头。
She was running late and we couldn't turn around.
没有任何借口！特别是无 没有你说你会做什么。
No, no! No excuses!
The bottom line is you didn't do what you said you were gonna do!
你离开你的兄弟！
You stranded your brother!
我很惭愧 问我的朋友回过头来,,,
It's embarrassing to ask my friend to turn around
去找八个孩子。
and go get some kid at the middle school.
如何做一个孩子他是你的兄弟！
What do you mean "some kid"? He's your brother!
你知道，我们会珍妮之前问。
And you know what? We've helped Janey out before.
学校是 在拐角处，这是没有问题的。
She lives right around the corner. It's no big deal.
宽恕。
Sorry.
你必须开始 想你想成为谁。
You know what, Samantha?
You need to start thinking long and hard about who you wanna be.
想成为的人 合作，有爱心，
Do you wanna be a cooperative person
who's compassionate and helps people out...
帮助人呢 还是你想成为一个无情的自大狂
...or do you wanna be a self-centered narcissist?
你说得对。我一个人 太可怕了，但他不是一个孩子了。
You know what? You're right. lam this horrible person.
But, honestly, he's not a baby anymore.
你应该把它看作。
You don't have to treat him like one.
这是在八年级和,,, 你只能回家，如果你喜欢。
He's in eighth grade, and he can find his way home if he wants to.
你知道吗当爱说话 你可以去，有一个谈话。
You know what?
When Gabi leaves, you and me are gonna have a chat.
- 狗急跳墙！ - 这很烂。
Awkward.
Dude, that sucks.
- 怎么样 - 营今晚。
Hey, man, what's up?
- 你来吗 - 谁去
Hey. We're going camping tonight.
You in?
我的哥哥，一个 托尼和他的朋友,,,,,,也许。
Uh. Who's going?
My brother, one of his friends, and Tony maybe.
我问我的母亲。
Yeah, let me check with my mom.
妈妈，我可以去追逐今天露营
Mom, can I go camping with Chase tonight?
在哪里
Camping? Where?
正在修建的家 他的家人。它几乎完成。
Uh, at that house that his family's building. It's pretty much finished.
会不会有,,,大人
Well, will any adults be there?
你哥哥是旧的。
His brother's a senior.
- 你有你的电话吗 - 是的。
You have your cell phone? Yeah.
负担
Is it charged? Mmm-hmm.
得到的电话号 和方向，他们的父母在柜台上的。
Okay, do me a favor.
Leave his parents' number and the address on the counter.
Okay-
那个！路去！
Yeah! What I'm talking about!
That's it.
不错。但是，这将是至高无上的。
You ready? Check this shit out.
That was all right, but this is gonna be badass.
让我们来看看 我所能做的。这是你的脸。
All right, let me see. Let me see what you can do.
All right. This is your face.
在这里打破了他的脸。
I'm about to break his face, right here.
好了，现在就来看看这个。 更好地获得移动。
All right, man. All right, now check this out. You might want to move.
Ow, that'd be painful.
In the kidneys, right? The stomach? Something.
Oh!
看看这个。
Check this out, man.
Pancreas.
这东西是致命的。
That shit's lethal.
这将是非常痛苦的。
Yeah, that would be painful.
一个啤酒。这是非常不错的。
Man, have a beer, man. That was awesome. Here.
冲泡时间。
It's beer 30, children.
Nice.
不，谢谢。
Uh, no, thanks.
来吧。
Come on, man.
你是FAG
What are you? A pussy?
我不喜欢喝啤酒。
I just don't feel like drinking a beer right now.
如果你畏缩啤酒，
Man, if you're too chickenshit to even have a beer,
一定要性交过一个女孩。
I know for a fact that you have never gotten any pussy.
- 你还好吗 - 清除。
Like you guys have.
什么时候
Sure have.
- 在夏天。 - 是谁
When?
Last summer.
大通和轻松 抓住了南希胡克。
- With who? - It was awesome.
Chase went down easy street and fucked this whore Nancy.
- 如此说。 - 这是。我会在哪里呢
At least, that's what he said.
不化妆。快速，你在哪里
I did. Would I lie?
在Tober。 她是一对夫妇的其他类型。
Bullshit. Quick, where were you?
At Taber's house.
And she fucked a couple other guys, too.
他的处女作是与使用！
Oh, man, his first piece of ass was sloppy seconds.
而你，梅森你是否已经有人吗
What about you, Mason? You ever got any?
已经打到他哭了一夜
Yeah, you ever made her, uh, howl into the night?
- 有时候。 - 真的吗
A few times. Really?
你确定。它怎么样
Yeah, right, what was her name? Lucky?
曼努埃拉・
No.Jennfien
不,,,,,,珍妮弗。
She doesn't live here, though. She's back in Houston.
不在这里。这是在休斯敦。
You're fucking lying.
说谎！
I don't care if you assholes believe me or not.
我不在乎，如果你不相信我。
Let me guess, you were pulling all kinds of ass back home,
换句话说，在休斯顿你是大阳,,,
but once you got down here, lefty.
但来到这里,,,,,,左脚！
Hey, fuck you.
你他妈的！我会， 但女孩在这里不想。
I would, but none of the girls here want to.
这不是他们想要的东西！ 这是你想要的。
Dude, it's not what they want, man, it's what you want.
真理。
True dat.
你知道吗 加入一个乐队去。
You know what you should do, join a band.
- 是吗 - 当然！
That's all it takes, man.
你甚至不用打出好成绩。
Oh,yeah? Fuck,yeah,dude.
你开始弹奏乐器 而女生排队吸你的家伙。
You don't even have to play that well.
You start playing your instrument,
and they line up to give you blowjobs.
而不是你。 女士们也顾不了那么多,,,
Except for you.
谁扮演在乐队的长笛。
It doesn't impress the ladies so much
when you play flute for the marching band.
我不是在军乐队！
I'm not in the fucking marching band.
你确定吗 我听说你打肉的长笛！
Oh, dude, you sure? I heard you play the skin flute.
我问一个问题。
All right, I got a question for you guys.
如果他们是如此之大，为什么 3白痴的一个星期五晚上
If you think you're so cool,
why you hanging out with a bunch of 8th graders on a Friday night?
闭嘴，Forrito。 你很幸运能来到这里。
Hey. Fuck you, you little penis wrinkle.
这是我们的营地。
You're lucky to even be here.
唯一的理由 你为什么在这里,,,
This is our camp-out.
The only reason you little cum gums are here
是查理的母亲 强行把他哥哥的设定，
is because fucking Charlie's mom made him
bring his little asshole brother
他给你带来了 2他妈的混蛋。
and then he drags along you little dice danglers.
他妈的混蛋！
Fucking fuzz nut, talking shit!
好吧。
It's all good, man.
这些儿童将 他的机会很快。
These little fuzz nuts are going to get their chance soon enough.
后来妓女来。
We got some whores coming by later.
- 是吗 - 就是这样！
- Yeah? - Hell yeah!
我知道大通打着什么。
Now, I know Chase will fuck anything.
我见过抓着墙壁。
I mean, I've seen this kid mount boulders before.
那么你们两个能得分
But what about you guys? You in?
随你。
- Whatever. - All right.
而你，伟大的风机
Good man. All right.
What about you, Peter Puffer?
我不知道。也许吧。
I don't know. Maybe.
如果你是同性恋都好。 明白了。但睡在那里。
Dude, it's okay to be gay. We understand.
Just, you know, sleep over there.
我不是同性恋。
I'm not gay-
给它时间。现在，你会发现。
Give it some time, man. You'll realize.
你他妈的！
Fuck y'all.
这就是我说的！
See, that's exactly my point, man.
有妓女。对我们 他妈的，看他们说什么。
Nah, but we don't have whores coming over.
We were just fucking with you to see what you'd say.
获得徽章。
And you just earned your vag badge.
把它放在旁边，你的卡母狗。
Put it next to your bitch card.
因为你是一个妓女。就拿这一点。
Yeah, 'cause, you know, you're a bitch.
- 由于小妓女。 - Putita！
Now hold this like the bitch you are, bitch.
这就是所谓的死的行程。
All right, this shit is called the death punch.
Whoa, Jesus!
Hey-
来了！有什么好。
You guys made it! Good.
Oh.
There you are. Oh, wow.
在这里，女主人。
And here you go, hostess.
谢谢。吃的东西
Oh, thank you. Can I get you a bite?
- 好。 - 谢谢。
Oh, that's cool. Thanks.
- 是吗 - 是的。
You did that?
Yeah. Wow.
- 多久你的工作 - 不多。
How long have you been doing that for?
Not very long. Um...
之后的夏令营。
I went to this camp thing just this past summer.
是否有涂鸦的阵营
They have a camp for graffiti?
他们称之为街头艺术。
Well, they call it "urban art." Oh.
为了看起来不那么非法的，但,,,
So it sounds, you know, less illegal
实际上使 获得免费喷漆。
but it was really just a way to get free spray paint.
大。
Cool. So is this your tag?
这是你的标签吗 所以,,,叫它,,,
Is that... Do they still call it...
是的，但他们只是字母， 我能做些什么。
Yeah, but you know, it's just letters that I'm good at writing.
è,,, C ,,, K，J，O。
It's a
E.
“Kecjo”。
"E-Z-J-O."
大。
Kez Jo. That's cool.
这意味着什么。
It doesn't really mean anything, though.
- 是你爸爸 - 是的。
Is that your dad?
- 你住在哪里 - 在休斯敦。
Yeah.
Where's he live?
你看他经常
In Houston.
Get to see him much?
部分周末和夏季。
Yeah. Some weekends and over the summer.
你是我妈妈的学生，对吗
Cool.
So, you're a student of my mom's, right?
是的，这是我,,,我有一类和她在一起。
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, I got one class with her.
这是好的。
Yeah, she's cool.
你好你是一个好老师
How's she doing? You know, is she a good teacher and everything?
挺好！很聪明 并且,,,,,,他关心的事情。
Yeah, she's great!
She's super-smart and she cares, you know.
做一流的有趣。
She makes it interesting.
可能是我最喜欢的老师。
She's probably even my favorite teacher.
我们找到了一种方法来放大 我们的iPod播放器在车内。
So, anyway, we figured out a way to rig up our iPods
to the external speakers on the ASB.
当我们到达一个村庄， 知道456是有,,,
So every time we come rolling into town,
因为我们跳，
you knew the 4-56 was there
在这里跳，跳到那里。
'cause we were bumping House of Pain.
It was like, "Jump around, jump around."
出了整个家庭。 是孩子们和,,,
And the whole family's coming outside,
母亲和父亲跳了一切。
you got the kids and, uh, the mom and the dad
我们扔糖果的孩子，
and they're all bouncing up and down,
we're throwing out candies for the kids
足球，娃娃和飞盘。
and soccer balls and Beanie Babies and Frisbees, uh,
香烟的成人和,,, 真正爱过的佳得乐。
smokes for the adults,
and, uh, they loved, they absolutely loved Gatorade.
但由于某种原因， 讨厌柠檬，酸橙的香味。
But for some reason, you know, they hated the lemon-lime flavor.
我不知道发生了什么事。
I don't know what it was.
或送人。
Yeah. Couldn't give it away.
多久是你吗
How long were you over there?
服务两个时期 在伊拉克，一个在波斯尼亚。
Uh, I did two tours in Iraq and one in Bosnia.
你争取
Wow.
Did you enlist?
是的，我是在保护 国家勉强读完高中。
Mmm-hmm. Yeah, I was, um, Army National Guard,
需要钱 大专及优厚的薪酬。
and, you know, coming straight out of high school,
needed money for college.
我做了我的任期。
Seemed like a decent paying job.
最后，我说，'如果我将返回 有事去改变世界。 “
And, uh, did my tour.
And whenever I got done I told them,
if there's a world-changing event, I'll come back.
三个月后 发生了什么事双塔和背部。
And, uh, three months later 9/11 happened, and I was back 9/12.
我很自豪的是，在整个 一次我在那里的456，
And I'm proud to say the 4-56, the whole time we were there,
从来没有失去任何人，没有之一。
we never lost a guy, not one casualty.
这是奇怪的，不寻常的
But is that odd? Is that unusual?
是的。
Yeah. Uh...
几乎是不可能的。
Almost impossible.
这些谁进来，以取代美国,,,
Like, the guys that came along after us and replaced us,
他们没有听到我们 建议。他们向后所做的一切。
they didn't listen to any of our advice.
They did, basically, the polar opposite of what we did,
他们失去了 七名士兵在第一个月。
and they lost seven guys in the first month.
那是什么 你做了什么不同
WOW.
What did you guys do differently?
我倾向于认为是 互相尊重的问题。
I like to think it's just a matter of mutual respect, you know.
所有的时间 致力于建立信任，
All the time we spent over there building trust,
他们摧毁了它三天。
these guys basically destroyed it in three days.
据当地人， 为什么我们没有
So, what did the locals think about why we're there?
油。简单明了。
- Oil, plain and simple. - Mmm.
梅森！
Hey, Mason. One last hit.
到达。
嘿！儿童俱乐部！ 已经下了车。
Hey-
Mickey Mouse Club. Get the fuck out of my car.
爬出窗口 背部或什么的。
Just crawl out the back window or something, man.
我会想念你。
I'm gonna miss you.
看你星期天晚上。
I'll see you on Sunday night.
给我发短信。
All right. You better text me.
你有什么胶
Mmm...
Do you have any gum? Um...
是的。这里。
Yeah, I do, actually. Here you go.
谢谢。再见。
Thanks. See ya.
接受帐户 党是,,,
And they're buying this party line that they're supposed to feel bad
愧疚与救赎 自己的退休，好像,,,
and trade off their own pension,
不管这会破坏这个国家。
as if that's what's been corrupting this nation.
Yeah, because those who heart Fox,
in my opinion, are being lied to.
Yeah, thank God for Wisconsin.
We have to follow that example.
You're right.
你好，梅森。现在是几H
Hey, Mason, what time is it?
类型,,, 12和15。
Uh, like 12315.
生日快乐。
Happy birthday.
生日快乐！
Happy birthday!
梅森！它是你的生日
Mason.
It's your birthday?
现在，它似乎。
Just now, I guess.
- 你多大了 - 15。
Yeah, how old are you?
Fifteen.
一个拥抱！
Fifteen. Give me a hug.
生日快乐。哇！
Happy birthday. Oh, my goodness!
有你喝醉了吗
Have you been drinking?
和你
Have you?
一点。和你
Yeah, a little. Have you?
一点点。
A little bit.
你是否也有,,,,,,
Have you been...
一点点。
A little bit.
on.
我要去睡觉。
Oh...
I'm gonna go to sleep.
我们谈论早上，好吗
Talk in the morning, huh?
爸爸！
Hey,Dad.
你好吗
Hey! How you doing? Mmm... Good.
- 谁拥有的车 - 这是我们的。
Whose car is that? That's our car.
合。
Hop on in there. Hey.
- 您好！ - 嘿，宝贝。
Hi, sweetie.
Oh...
您好，库珀！
Hey, Cooper.
怎么样了
Hey! How's it going?
你好，兄弟。它是如此的可爱。
Hello, little brother.
我们不能代替 管道的一部分
He's so cute.
Can we just replace that part of the pipe?
不，不行的。一切都年久失修。
No, is no good. Everything is no good.
- 所有的一切 - 是的，一切。米拉。
Everything. Yes, mira.
这是,,,
This one is...
- 更强 - 这是更好的。是啊是啊。
Stronger.
Yes. This is better, yes,yes,yes.
感谢您的相机 你给了梅森。
Hey, listen, thanks for that camera you got Mason.
- 一个梅森喜欢摄影。 - 是的。
Oh, yeah, Mason's all into the photography. He's loving that thing.
他说，他希望把 她的衣柜里在黑暗的房间。
Yeah, I know.
He's actually talking about turning his, uh, closet into a darkroom.
红灯亮并透露。一切。
Like the red light and the developing, the whole nine...
- 你不是有问题 - 我不会看到他了一个星期。
You all right with that?
I probably won't see him for a week. Oh, yeah. Right.
他的乐趣。
But he's having a good time.
至少，他的重点是什么。
At least he's focused on something. Yeah. Yeah.
我喜欢。
That's what I like. Yeah, he's all about it.
这种自身。
Okay, let's go grande.
好了，就到“大”。
It's good? It's better, yes. It's good.
很好。这是更好的，是的。
你很聪明，你应该学习。
You know, you're smart. You should be in school.
我喜欢学习， 我需要它，但,,,
Oh, I like school, I need school,
这很难。我整天上班,,,
but it's hard, I working all day.
去上夜校！教育 社区三级。它也不是很贵。
Go to night school at community college. It's pretty affordable.
做好的房子。看上去很不错。
You're doing a nice job with the house. It's looking great.
- 谢谢。 - 很好。
Oh, thanks. Really great.
我们固定在这里和那里。 我们得到了它的廉价拍卖。
Yeah, you know, some fix-its here and there.
现在我知道为什么了。
We got a good deal on a foreclosure, so now I'm finding out why.
Yeah, really. Hey,bud! Hey.
- 生日快乐！ - 怎么样
Happy birthday, huh? What's that?
这是我们的新车！
What's that? That's our new car. Get in it.
过来。
All right. Have a good weekend.
有一个美好的周末。
- 您好！ - 你好吗
How you doing?
- 很高兴见到你。 - 我也是。
Good to see you. You, too.
Hey!
你好吗
Hey, how are you?
Ooh...
你看起来棒极了。看！
You look great. Ooh!  Thanks.
Look at him! Aw, he's got Mason's nose.
梅森的鼻子！
- Yeah, isn't he cute? - Yeah.
准备好了！我们有很长的路要走。
- All right! - Love you guys.
- 再见了，山姆！ - 小心驾驶！
We got a big drive ahead of us.
Bye, Sam.
You guys drive safe.
我们将在明天晚上。
All right. Well, we'll be back tomorrow night.
再见了，亲爱的。 我很高兴你出生！
Bye, honey. I'm so glad you were born!
这是汽车,,,安妮 那你驾驶庞蒂亚克GTO
So, this is like Annie's car and you drive the GTO?
婴儿座椅不走与其他。
I guess you can't really put a baby seat in that thing.
号正是我不得不卖掉。
Yeah, no. But I had to sell that anyway.
什么
You what?
是的，我不得不卖掉。
Yeah, I had to sell that.
还有,,,,,,你不再有
So it's gone?
集电极 加利福尼亚州支付我$ 22,000元。
Yeah, some sucker collector from California
我很好，因为 我用现金支付的。
paid 22 grand for it, which is great
'cause I basically got to pay for this in cash.
他8500美元很久以前已经支付。
I only paid $8,500 for that thing way back when.
在一般情况下，汽车 他们是可怕的投资。
Cars are generally a terrible investment, you know.
把它拿出来的机构 你会得到一辆二手车，
Soon as you drive them off the lot,
然后对值减小。
you got a used car on your hands,
and the value's only dropping from there.
但是，如果照顾，
But if you take care of it, you know,
你是幸运的，这是一个经典，
and you get lucky and it's a classic,
价格上涨。
the value starts going up again.
有些人付出几十万 美元的福特Shelby眼镜蛇。
Shit, you got guys paying hundreds of thousands of dollars
for some Shelby Cobra.
什么
What?
你不记得了
You don't remember?
我怎么记得吗
Remember what? Really?
真的吗
你告诉我 这将是我的，当我转身16。
You said that was going to be my car when I turned 16.
什么没有，从来没有说过。
What? No, I didn't. I never said that.
我记得。我是在小学三年级，
I remember. I was in third grade
而你背着我的房子 安东尼・格尔，因为这是他的生日。
and you were taking me over to Anthony Nadar's house for his birthday,
我们花了几圈，因为 我们到得早。
and we were there early, so we gave him a ride around the block,
你谈到多少 你喜欢你的车。
and he was talking about how much he loved your car,
“这将是梅森的时候，他变成16。”
and so you were all like, "Oh, this is gonna be Mason's when he turns 16."
首先，我不记得说。 二，从来不说什么。从来没有。
All right, first off, I have no memory of that, all right?
Second of all, I would never say that. Never
但是你做到了。
Oh, you did, though.
梅森,,,
What?
Mason.
和你的妹妹吗 难道我要忘了呢
Come on, what about your sister?
来吧。这公平吗
I'm just gonna forget about her?
Come on, how's that fair? Huh?
安东尼・格尔，脸,,,什么
Anthony Nagar. What...
来吧！
Are you...
Oh, come on!
你不能,,,
I mean, you're not...
你可以把一张脸 安葬，如果你想要的。
Look, you can sit there like there's a death in the family, all right,
但是，这个问题很简单:这是我的车。
but bottom line is, that was my car. All right?
我买了它，我照顾他， 我做了我想要它。
I paid for it, I took care of it,
and I can do whatever I want with it. All right?
对不起，如果你有其他的希望。
I'm sorry if you had other ideas about it, but when you get older,
但是，当你长大，你会 攒起来买自己的车。
you can save up and buy a car of your own.
而且是“酷”，因为我是。
Be cool like I used to be.
或者,,,,,,你可以买一辆面包车。
Or you can get a minivan.
你妈妈让你看这个
Does your mom actually let you watch this?
是的，她很喜欢这一点。
Yeah. She likes it, too.
Oh, my God.
Okay, well, have you ever seen her in concert?
你有没有见过活的
No, but she's coming to Houston in April.
没有，但来到休斯敦四月。
She's coming to Houston? Mmm-hmm.
你来休斯顿吗
Your dad and I could get you tickets and you could stay with us.
我们可以给你弄到票 您可以和我们呆在一起。
That'd be great! Yeah.
- 这将是伟大的！ - 是的。
安妮，你会与我擦肩而过 拥有从梅森的礼物呢
- Hey, Annie? - Yup.
Will you get me the little birthday present for Mason?
- 在这里，亲爱的。 - 需要一点解释。
Here, babe. All right.
This one needs a little explanation, okay?
打开它。
Open it up.
我把它称为“磁盘 黑色甲壳虫“。
I call that the Beatles Black Album.
因为它是,,,
What it is, is the best of John, Paul, George and Ringo,
最好的约翰，乔治， 保罗和林戈分离后。
solo, post-breakup.
谢谢。
Thanks.
简而言之， 聚集带你。
Basically, I put the band back together for you.
当你听到的很多东西 他们单飞，百无聊赖。
Whenever you listen to too much of the solo stuff,
it kind of becomes a drag, you know?
但是，你把彼此相邻，
But you put them next to each other, right,
和互利上升。
and they start to elevate each other,
然后你意识到。
and then you can hear it.
是披头士！
It's The Beatles, you know?
我不知道。我认为，保罗总是首选。
I don't know. I think I always just liked Paul the best.
不要紧。你不理解的想法。
It doesn't matter, you know, you're missing the point.
没有最喜欢的披头士！这是 我说的话。问题是平衡。
There is no favorite Beatle!
That's what I'm saying. It's in the balance.
那是什么让妓女 摇滚乐队是世界上最大的！
That's what made them the greatest fucking rock band
in the world, okay?
有十年 分散的音乐。
And there's this decade of music out there
它经过精心定位， 组织和整洁的你,,,
that's been scattered, all right,
and now it has been carefully found, arranged and ordered for you
您慈祥的爸爸。
by your loving father.
很有条理，整洁 几次爱你的爸爸。
Very arranged and very organized,
over and over again by your loving father.
当然！是的！看看这个。看看这个。
Yes, yes, yes.
So, I mean, look at that, look at that.
前四个问题，第2卷。
Uh, top of volume ll, first four tracks,
从“波段上运行”到“我滴神啊” 一个“嫉妒型”到“摄影”。
you've got Band on the Run into My Sweet Lord
into Jealous Guy into Photograph. Come on!
您好！
It's like the perfect segue.
这是完美的过渡！
You got Paul, who takes you to the party,
保罗带你参加一个聚会。 乔治你说话神。
George who talks to you about God,
约翰说: “实在不行，关于爱与痛”。
John is just, "No, it's about love and pain,"
和林戈说:“我们不能享受 我们所拥有的时刻“
and then Ringo who just says,
"Hey. Can't we enjoy what we have while we have it?"
- 这是一个很好的专辑。真的。 - 伟大的。
It's a good record. I shit you not.
Cool.
- 嗨，悬崖！ - 您好！你好吗
Hey, there, Cliff. Hey, how you doing?
Good. How you doing? Hi, birthday boy!
- 很高兴见到你！ - 很高兴见到你。
It's good to see you.
Ah, it's great to see you. Yeah.
You made it all right, huh?
Yeah, we sure did. We sure did.
How are you, darling?
- 将结冰。 - 等待！
Let's just get this one... All right, we ready?
Yeah.
Wait.
山姆！
Hey, Sam.
来吧。
Wait, wait, wait. Come on.
他们仍然睡着了吗
Hey, still sleeping here?
Oh, yeah.
Hey, buddy.
Oh!
一个愿望，一个愿望！
Make a wish, make a wish.
礼品！等待！ 在这里，亲爱的。
Real good! Presents! Wait, wait, wait. Here, sweetie.
山姆，你能带 小刀切除吗
Sam, would you get us a knife so we can cut this up?
希望你喜欢它。 我听说你没有一个，所以,,,
All right.
I hope you like it. I heard you didn't have one, so.
一本圣经！这是你的第一个圣经！
It's a Bible. This is your first Bible.
有了你的名字。
Look, there's your name.
等待，等待。
Wow. In gold. And wait, wait, wait.
Look at this.
这是一个大喜的版本。因此， 耶稣说一切都是红色的。
It's a red-letter edition,
and that means that everything that Jesus said is in red.
- 谢谢。 - 你喜欢它很好。
Thank you. You like it? All right.
亲爱的，生日快乐。
I love you, sweetie. Happy birthday.
这是属于我们的。
And this one's from us.
Oh, yeah, here.
这不是梦。降低你的期望。
It's not going to make all your dreams come true here.
没有，但你需要它。这是一个,,,
Just keep your expectations low.
No, you need it. It's...
你必须有！你需要它。
Come on, right? You gotta have it. You need this.
- 未来一辈子。 - 和衬衫是蓝色的。
You got life ahead of you.
And the shirt is blue.
舞蹈,,,,,,面试,,,,,, 我会起皱。
You got dances and job interviews.
Here, I'm going to get it all wrinkled here.
梅森。
Mason? Come here, son. Uh-oh.
来到这里，儿子。
SIGHING)
Desenfúndala。
Pull that Off.
这是一个20口径猎枪。
There's a 20-gauge shotgun. Wow.
我爸爸给我当 我比你年轻一点。
My dad gave it to me when I was a little younger than you,
他的父亲给了它。
and his dad gave it to him.
你15，我想是你的。
Well, you're 15 and I'd like for you to have it, all right?
有什么好。
Here, you hold it.
持有。
Yeah?
谢谢。
Thank you. Congratulations, son.
恭喜你，儿子。 我教你清洁它，拍它。
I'll teach you how to clean it,
teach you how to fire it.
我会告诉你一个小保安。
I'll teach you a little bit of safety.
Amartíllala。
Now cock it. All right, there you go.
你想要的是对齐 正面与背面。
Now, what you want to do is line up the front sight with the back sight.
你看到的小“V”
Here, you see this little V right here? Mmm-hmm.
- 这将您注册 - 中的一个即可。
Now which one you aiming at?
是中间好吧。
Uh, the middle can.
The middle can? All right. Mmm-hmm.
拍摄自由裁量权。
Now fire at will, all right?
Ho! Whoa! Yeah!
在意。当心。很好。
All right, watch out, watch out. Whoa. Be careful. All right.
准备好了吗
Ready?
Pull!
你出手有点低。
Oh, you hit a little low.
预期上升，然后进行拍摄。 这是最好的时候了。
Wait till it gets up high, then shoot, all right?
'Cause then it's a better aim coming down.
请记住，第二个触发器。
Remember, second trigger.
Mmm-hmm.
Ready? Mmm-hmm.
Pull!
你看那个！你打的吧
Look what you did! Well, you nailed it, didn't you?
- 你感觉如何 - 好吧。
How did that feel? Felt good.
Yeah, it felt good. Good.
报价永远在一起
Well, I want for us to be together forever
一个伟大的，无论你在哪里
But to wander wherever I may
要容易和非正式
I want you to be easy and casual
但仍是人谁是
But still demand I stay
嗯，你知道我们 为保持神秘
I want for you to know me completely
But still remain mysterious
相信大家深深 但始终无惧
Consider everything deeply
But still remain fearless
滚动到顶部，从窗台往下看
Climb to the top Look over the ledge
和赤脚跳舞 在剃刀边缘
Dance barefoot on a razor's edge
梦回大， 陷入危险的东西
Reach for the stars Grab a tiger by the tail
如果我尝试永远不会失败
If I don't try, I'll never fail
如果你脱光房子骰子
If you go home You're rolling the dice
不应该得到在河里湿两次
Can't step in the same river twice
如果你爱变成恨太
You love too much It'll turn to hate
如果你从来没有回家了，你 后来你永远不会
You never leave home You'll never be late
如果你吃太多，你发胖
You eat too much You're gonna get fat
如果你买的狗猫生气
If you buy a dog You'll piss off your cat
深吸一口气，享受骑
So take a deep breath and enjoy the ride
对于来港定居人士及 标题是并行
'Cause arrivals and departures Run side by side
他们是我们的第一个观众。
Oh!
You're our first audience, you know?
梅森要求 排练是在路上。
Mason demanded we work on it the whole time.
- 令人敬佩 - 缺乏工作。
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
一个星期后 - 不知道 为什么托马斯是不是第一次 -
It's a work in progress.
A week later, we don't know why
Thomas wasn't there the first time, uh,
但一周 后来，汤姆返回,,,
but a week later, Thomas comes back
并与其他弟子去。
and joins the other disciples.
他们说:“耶和华是活的， ！因此，我们所看到的！ “”我不相信，
They say, "The Lord's alive, we saw him!"
“直到他们把我的手放进他的身边，
"I won't believe it until I put my finger into his side,
“，感觉伤口在他的手里。”
"and I wanna see those nail prints in his hands."
就在这时到达 耶稣站在他旁边。
About that time, here comes Jesus
standing right next to him, okay?
并期待在托马斯。 你看，他觉得托马斯的耻辱吗
And he turns to Thomas. Don't you know, Thomas felt some shame.
托马斯看着他，说: “托马斯，摆在我的身边你的手。”
He turns to Thomas and says,
"Thomas, here, stick your finger in my side.
“看我的伤口，是我！”
"Look at these nail prints. It's me."
和托马斯说: “我的主，我的上帝。事情，我想。”
And Thomas says, "My Lord and my God, I believe."
耶稣说:“那就好。”
And Jesus said, "Well, that's good,
“不过祝福 那些谁相信没有看到。 “
"but blessed are those who can believe without seeing."
这是很容易当 你可以看到。和感觉。和触摸。
It's a lot easier when you can see and feel and touch,
在我们的例子中， 我们还没有看到人。
but like us, we haven't seen him in the flesh,
大家有没有觉得在人。
we haven't felt him in the flesh,
但是，我们已经感觉到 在我们的精神;少一些。
but we have experienced him in the spirit.
我希望你也这样做。
At least, I have, and I hope y'all have, too.
泻湖是在这里。
The pond's right up here.
- 几楼！ - 是的。
Ooh, it's low.
Yeah.
我爸爸可以带他们 钓鱼下一次。
You know, my dad could take you fishing
next time you're here if you want.
Thanks.
Hi, baby. What's goin' on?
- 我就在这里等着。 - 你要我留下来吗
No, I think we're just gonna hang here for a minute.
- 不，这很好。 - 你确定 - 是的，谢谢你。
You want me to stay with you?
No, it's okay. You sure?
Yeah. Thanks.
梅森，为什么还有那么过时
Mason, why are you such a stick-in-the-mud?
也不知道你在说什么。
What are you even talking about?
难道他们不关心回来 库珀的洗礼20天
You guys don't mind coming back here on the 20th, do you,
for Cooper's baptism?
- 没问题。 - 山姆
No, that's fine. Sam?
谢谢。 这意味着很多安妮和她的家人。
I appreciate it.
It means a lot to Annie and her folks, you know.
是我们受洗我们吗
Were we baptized?
这不是白白 感兴趣的你灵魂的状态。
I wasn't the least bit concerned with the state of your soul.
我现在该我们做的， 如果你想。你和库柏一起
We can do it now, though, if you want.
No, I think I'm all right.
头淹没
You and Cooper together, you know.
Dunk your heads.
你是不是会成为 神人吧爸爸
You're not becoming one of those God people, are you, Dad?
这意味着什么
And what's that supposed to mean, huh?
我听到了！
I can hear you!
我觉得猎枪 将在主场更好。
Oh, wow.
I think that shotgun should live at my house, huh?
你妈妈会不会喜欢它。
I don't think your mom would love that.
当心，山姆。我会告诉你怎么做。
Look out, Sam.
Let me show you how it's done.
好了，爸爸！
Nice, Dad.
即使我能！
Still got the goods, hmm?
- 你有没有来过多久，梅森 - 我不知道。
How long you been in here, Mason?
我有。全班。
I'm not sure.
I'm sure.
All class.
- 你完成你的图片日记 - 还没。
Did you complete your image diary?
Not yet.
和你的数码联系表
Completed your, uh, digital contact sheet?
我缺乏。 但没多久。
Not quite, but it's not gonna take me long.
“还没。” “我没有。”
Not yet. Not quite.
当时 暗房是课外。
Dark room time is extra-curricular.
实际上，如今的 甚至不需要到这里来。
I mean, technically, you don't ever have to be in here these days,
当然不是，如果它 你还没有完成你的任务。
and certainly not until you've completed your assignments.
这里的问题。
That's the deal.
对不起。
Sorry.
我很担心，梅森。
I'm worried about you, Mason.
- 为什么 - 我会告诉你。
Why is that?
图像交货,,,
I'll tell you why.
The images you're turning in, they're cool.
酷。您正在浏览 唯一的东西。
You're looking at things in a really unique way.
你有这么多的天赋。
Got a lot of natural talent.
谢谢。
Thanks.
是的，但是这还没有得到 拿铁在这个世界上。
Yeah, but that and 50 cents
will just get you a cup of coffee in this old world.
我接触过很多 有才华的人，多年来。
I've met a lot of talented people over the years.
有多少人成功 作为专业人士,,,
How many of them made it professionally
没有纪律，决心， 而大量的工作
without discipline, commitment
and a really good work ethic?
我告诉你！ 在我可以指望两个手指。
I can tell you. I can count it on two fingers.
零！
Zero.
它不会发生，梅森。 这个世界太有竞争力的。
It's not gonna happen for you, Mason.
The world is too competitive.
太多有才华的人 谁愿意去努力，
There are too many talented people who are willing to work hard,
并且还有谁没有太多的傻瓜,,,
and a butt load of morons who are untalented
天赋，但 他们已经准备好提高自己。
who are more than willing to surpass you.
许多 坐在课堂了。
As a matter of fact, a lot of them are sitting in that classroom
你知道他们做了什么
out there right now, hmm?
任务，这是什么 你应该做的，
You know what they're doing?
They're doing their assignments.
但你不是。 你在这里。为什么呢
Which is what you're supposed to be doing, but you're not.
You're in here.
Now why is that?
你是特别的，梅森
You special, Mason?
不可以，但在关于道德 工作中，我觉得我努力工作。
No, but the things you're talking about,
like work ethic or whatever,
I feel like I do work pretty hard.
很多时候，我花 整个周末拍照。
I spend the whole weekend taking pictures a lot of times.
喜欢足球，梅森
You like football, Mason?
- 不多。 - 我知道。
Not really.
所以，我只是下令 你盖的大学比赛今天。
Yeah, I know you don't.
That's why I've just assigned you
to shoot the football game tonight. Okay?
它开始于7和30提前到达。 我想要的照片全卡，
It starts at 7:30, I want you to get there early,
300的图像。我希望他们降低，
I want you to shoot a full card, 300 images, I want them downloaded,
我希望他们举办 我想看看周一早。
I want them sorted, and I want to see them very first thing Monday.
想知道为什么吗
You want to know why I'm doing this?
武卫,,,
I guess.
你怎么想，梅森
Who do you want to be, Mason?
你是做什么
What do you want to do?
我要拍照。
I want to take pictures.  Make art.
艺术创作。
Any dipshit can take pictures, Mason.
任何白痴 你可以拍照，梅森。
Art, that's special.
艺术是别的东西。
What can you bring to it that nobody else can?
你能贡献 没有人可以吗
这就是我试图找出。
That's what I'm trying to find out.
加倍努力。
Try harder.
也许20年 克里斯蒂特灵顿先生叫老,,,
Maybe in 20 years you can call old Mr. Turlington and you can say,
然后你告诉他“谢谢你，先生”,,,,,,
"Thank you, sir,
对于大谈在黑暗的房间。
"for that terrific darkroom chat we had that day."
回去上课，开始工作。
Get back to class and do your work.
你走路有点怪异。
Hey, man, you're walkin' a little funny.
去你妈的。
Fuck you.
我说。他们在很长一段时间。
I'm just saying, you guys were in there for a long time.
希望对你有支付晚餐。
Just hope he bought you dinner first.
梅森！吃，亲爱的！
Mason! Honey, come down for dinner.
萨曼莎！还没有上传 与描述照片
Samantha! You didn't post these pictures and their descriptions?
来吧。上周日在拍卖结束。
Come on. This auction is gonna end on Sunday, honey.
你要发布。
You've gotta get those posted.
我们该怎么办
Why are we even doing this?
它看起来像一个旧货店。
It's like an online junk shop.
- 我还以为你有一份好工作。 - 我有什么。
I thought you had a good job.
但房子有很多的费用。
I do. We're what you call house poor.
每个人都有贡献。 你哥哥拍的照片,,,
Everyone's got to do their part.
你必须合作。
Your brother took the pictures.
谁买这狗屎
You have to help.
山姆，小心你说的话。 不要不尊重你的母亲。
Who even buys this shit?
Hey. Sam, watch your mouth, all right?
要 屋顶在你的头上，对不对
Don't disrespect your mother.
You like a roof over your head, don't you?
和电量充至您的手机吗
Yeah, and you like having electricity
so that you can charge your cell phone?
明年我也不会。 我应该有乐趣，在过去的一年。
I'm not even gonna be here next year.
I'm a senior. I should be having fun.
那美丽的指甲。
Nice nails.
该画的女孩在学校。
Yeah, some girl did that in sixth period.
- 你会让它 - 通牙釉质，我想。
You planning on keeping them?
Until it comes off, l guess.
去年夏天， 现在耳环钉,,,
Last summer it was the earrings, and now the nails.
没有一个投资组合相结合
You got a purse to go with all that?
很多做它看起来“酷”。
A lot of guys do that. He's just trying to be cool.
当我在 高,,,和工作，
When I was in high school, having a job,
负责， 买车，
being responsible, being able to afford a car, that was cool.
是“酷”。
Mason, honey,
梅森，请去找水。
why don't you get you and your sister some water.
嘿嘿。说够克里斯蒂特灵顿 艺术与搭戏的照片。
Hey, man, Turlington says to cut the artsy crap and shoot the game.
因此，有一点你的镜头。
So take your lens and point it that way.
- 上帝。 - 我们将离开这里。
Jesus Christ.
Also, we got a ride.
他们给我们的门票聚会。 我们在比赛结束后到来。
McCormick's gonna take us to the party.
We're gonna head out after the game.
You're goin', okay?
聚会的照片。
Okay-
Shoot the game.
第一！这是怎么回事这是怎么回事
First one! What was that? What was that? What is up?
- 你好，梅森。 - 你好吗
Hey, what's up? Hey.
好吧。怎么你在这里多久了多久
How's it goin'?
Pretty good.
How long have you been here?
- 我不知道。一会儿。 - 一会儿
I don't know. Awhile, I guess.
Awhile?
我觉得有这么多,,,
I just feel like there are so many things that I could be doing
我可以做的，并 我想要做的，但没有。
and probably want to be doing that I'm just not.
为什么不呢
Why aren't you?
我认为这是恐惧,,,,,, 什么人会想到。
I mean, I guess it's just being afraid of what people would think.
- 你知道，试验。 - 是的。
You know, judgment. Yeah.
这很容易说，“不，我 不在乎别人怎么想“
I guess it's really easy to say like,
"I don't care what anyone else thinks,"
- 但每个人问津。 - 这是正确的。
but everyone does, you know? Exactly.
在后台。
Deep down.
我生气了很多人 与谁我联系,,,
I find myself so furious at all these people that I'm in contact with
因为我控制 或什么的，但是,,,
just for controlling me or whatever,
他们甚至不知道他们这样做。
but, you know, they're not even aware they're doing it.
Yeah.
而在这个世界上 那里没有人玩完美,,,
So, in this perfect world, where no one's controlling you,
有什么不同什么样的变化
what's different? What changes?
一切。我只是想 做你想做的。
Everything.
I mean, I just wanna be able to do anything I want,
这让我觉得活着。
because it makes me feel alive.
而不是给我 正常的外观。
As opposed to giving me the appearance of normality.
不管它是什么。
Whatever that means.
我没有多想。
I don't think it means much.
你是一个有点怪异，你知道吗
You're kinda weird, you know that?
Yeah?
它是一种恭维
Is that a compliment?
我不知道。想成为怪异
I don't know. Do you wanna be weird?
我不想吓唬,,, 孩子们在公园什么的。
I mean, I don't want to like scare kids at the park, or anything like that.
我喜欢跟你说话。
I really like talking with you.
我通常不尝试发声 我的思想，感情，或任何东西。
I don't usually even try to vocalize my thoughts
or feelings or anything.
从来没有听起来不错。 话是,,,,,,愚蠢。
I don't know, it never sounds right. Words are stupid.
而你为什么告诉我吧
So, why are you trying with me?
我不知道。我想是因为我感觉很舒服。
I don't know. I guess I feel comfortable.
我很高兴。
I'm glad.
嗨，吉姆。对不起，我迟到了。
Hey, Jim.
I'm sorry I'm so late.
你有什么时间去
What time are you supposed to be home?
我不知道。前一段时间。
I don't know. A while ago.
一个男人，而,,, 三十分钟一个小时
While ago like, 30 minutes ago, an hour ago?
没有人知道你在哪儿 直到你的姐姐说。
'Cause truthfully nobody even knew
where you were until your sister told us.
她到达较早。
She's been home for a while.
对不起。
I'm sorry.
我听说了很多最近。
Yeah, been hearin' a lot of that lately.
但是,,,,,,你真的不关心。
See,but you don't actually care.
你来来去去，在您的休闲。
You just kinda come and go as you please,
你不关心，如果您 母亲而言，
and you don't care if your mom's upset,
或者你应该到什么时候。 是故事
or what time you gotta be home.
Is that what's up?
- 我不知道该说些什么。 - 停止牙牙学语！
I don't know what to tell you.
Stop mumbling!
你说句话啊！
You know, speak up!
不明白 字。听起来像“mhmmm”,,,,,,
I can't understand a word comin' out of your mouth.
It's just like...
而我要问的问题，你只是,,,
And I ask you questions and you just...
它可以一天不 每个人都他妈的跟我
Can I just have one day where everyone isn't all over my ass?
我他妈的
I'm up your ass?
这是我的家。
This is my house. All right?
如果你想住在我家，来 当你说你会。
If you wanna live in my house,
then you get home when you say you're gonna be home.
你知道吗，吉姆你不是我爸爸。
You know, Jim, you're not my dad.
我知道我不是你爸爸。 你知道我是怎么知道的
No, I'm not your dad.
因为我在这里。
You know how I know that? 'Cause I'm actually here.
我是谁拥有的工作之一，支付 账单，照顾你，你的妈妈,,,,,,
I'm the guy with the job, payin' the bills,
takin' care of you, your mom, your sister, huh? Huh?
你的妹妹,,,,,,咦是吗
I'm that guy!
这就是我！
更正
- 美好的一天。 - 美好的一天。
Morning. Morning.
你们谁 用楼下的浴室昨晚
Hey. Which one of you guys used the downstairs bathroom last night?
我不知道。这不是我的。
I don't know. I didn't.
高，他叫什么名字
That tall guy, what's his name?
- 菲利普 - 是的，菲利普。
Phillip?
Yeah, Phillip. He did it. Can Phillip read?
菲利普读
You know, there's a big sign on the door.
牌子，上面写着: “不要使用这个卫生间坏了。”
It says, "Do not use this bathroom, it's broken."
就那么难吗
I mean, how difficult is that?
我不知道。对不起。
I don't know. I'm sorry.
我认为这将使房子出售。
I think I'm gonna put the house on the market.
为什么呢
Why?
这是非常大的，我们。
This house is too big for us.
很快，你要上大学。 它是非常昂贵的。巴斯塔。
You're going to school eventually.
It's too expensive. I'm done.
你买了什么
Why did you even buy it in the first place then?
因为我爱服用 糟糕的决定在我的生活。
Because I really enjoy making poor life decisions,
而且有你在贫穷的边缘。
keeping us on the brink of poverty.
我花了一半 我生命中购买垃圾,,,
I've spent the first half of my life acquiring all this crap,
现在我会去其他 quitándomelas半价。
and now I'm gonna spend the second half of my life
是吗像什么
getting rid of all this stuff.
Really? Like what?
我摇了摇假两夫妻。
Well, I got rid of a couple husbands,
现在是到 按揭，维修，
now I'm gonna get rid of a mortgage,
小饰物，保险,,, 业主，物业税，
some maintenance, the tchotchskes,
the homeowner's insurance, the property tax, the plumbing.
管道,,
你知道吗现在 妈咪会更加和尚。
You know what? From now on,
lam gonna be Mommy Monk.
简单。独身。
Simple. Celibate.
这太烂了，妈妈。
Don't be gross, Mom.
好。然后，我将是一个 可怜的母狗带大房子。
Fine.
I'll be a poor whore with a big house.
听起来是不是更好呢
Is that better? Hmm?
Okay.
梅森，请 不要离开我脏板。
Mason, please, don't leave me that dirty dish to wash.
所有的一天，我洗碗。
I do dishes all day.
好吧！你是一个专业。您可以 洗一两个人你可怜的母亲。
Oh, great! Honey, then you're a professional.
Come on, you could do one or two more for your poor old mom.
- 行。 - 谢谢。
Okay-
Thank you.
想要吗
You want one?
也感动。我看了所有的时间。
on, God!
She didn't even touch them, seriously.
为了谁，你观察到退化。
I watched her the whole time.
I bet you did watch her, you little pervert.
这就像约会。
It's like we're on a date.
身体健康！
Cheers.
一个浪漫的夜晚。
It's a night of romance.
但我不会吻。
Yeah, except I'm not gonna kiss you.
虽然我吸你。
I will blow you, though.
梅森！有紧急的休息室。
Mason! We are in the weeds out here!
í尽快做越好。
I'm goin' as fast as I can.
我一定是糊涂话。 因为最近我看到4月份聊天。
Oh, then I must be confused then,
我们必须重新沙拉。
'cause I just saw you chattin' it up with April,
when I got a salad bar that needs a refill,
6一个表，两个表 4，我不能用，
I got a six-top, two four-tops I can't use
因为他们是肮脏的。
because they haven't been bussed!
恩里克没来。我做我可以。
Enrique is not here. I'm tryin'.
好了，我们就麻烦了。
Well, while you're tryin', we're dyin'!
那你告诉客户
What am I supposed to tell my customers?
“很抱歉的脏盘子， 但梅森做什么，他可以。 “
"Oh, I'm sorry that your table's got dirty plates on it,
"but Mason's trying.
“这就是他告诉我的。”
"At least that's what he told me.
“4月份之后调情 吃了过虾“。
"After he was flirtin' with April and eatin' your leftover shrimp."
我知道，今天是困难的。 但我想告诉你一件事。
Now it is a challenge out there today, I know,
but I wanna share something with you.
我已经定你 服务员在今年夏天。
I got you pegged for fry cook this summer,
这是一个很多的责任。
and that's a lot more responsibility.
而更多的钱。
It's also more money. How's that sound?
你有什么感想
Good.
好吧。
I know you can handle that money,
我知道你可以用这笔钱，但 你可以处理的责任
but can you take the responsibility?
我想是这样。因为我相信你。
I think you can, because I believe in you.
我需要你在休息室。
But I need you on the floor.
离开菜肴和着急。
Now leave the dishes. Giddy up.
来吧。不要让我失望！
All right, come on! Don't let me down!
它是否会奏效吗 是发电机不给更多的麻烦
Well, so it's runnin' okay? That alternator's not messin' up anymore?
好吧。准备好了行程。
No, it's fine. It's up for the trip.
Good.
你会看到在奥斯汀你姐姐
Are you gonna see your sister when you guys are in Austin?
是啊，他说我可以留下来 在他的UNI宿舍。
Yeah, she said I can stay at her dorm, which is cool.
我觉得你的伴侣 旅行，所以没问题。
And I guess her roommate's out of town, so it's no big deal.
你已经申请了UT斯达康 您所要发送的形式
All right. Did you apply there yet?
Did you get that application in to UT?
还没有，但希娜 实际上是接受了。
Not yet, but Sheena's pretty much in, though.
如果这就是你想要去的,,,
Right. Well, if you know that's where you wanna go,
你应该postularte 为早日接受。
you should probably do that early acceptance thing, you know?
让他们知道你是 一个男人，谁知道他想要什么。
Seriously, let 'em know you're a man who knows what he wants.
有些坚定性 这辈子取得了很大成就。
Yeah.
A little bit of decisiveness goes a long way in this life, all right?
- 无 - 是的。
Yeah. Great.
和工作怎么样了
And what about work? How's that goin'?
好吧。今天是 一个糟糕的一天。他错过了一个人。
Uh, I don't know. It's all right.
Today kind of sucked. This guy didn't show up.
但毫无疑问，它给 换个角度看人生。
But it's definitely an interesting perspective on the world.
人是猪！
People are slobs.
当他们问你， 说“泥瓦匠做的非常好。”
Well, when people ask me about you, I say to them,
“你有一份工作。清理一切。”
"Mason, he's doing great.
"He's got a job, he's really cleanin' up."
打个招呼安妮和库珀。
AH right, say hi to Annie and Cooper, will you?
问好你的大哥哥。 “你好，兄弟。”
Say hi to your big brother. "Hey, big brother."
你好安妮。你好，朋友。
Hey, Annie. Hey, kiddo.
说再见。
Can you say bye-bye?
Bye-bye!
再见。
We'll see you soon.
开车时一定要小心。
All right. Well, be careful when you're driving, all right?
不要发短信什么的。
Don't be texting, don't be doing any of that. All right, just...
您奥比万。 专注和耐心,,,,,,不是吗
You're Obi-Wan. You're centered, patient. Right?
三辆车关注 在前面，两个在后面。
You watch three cars ahead, two behind.
它有两个坏 导致发生事故。
Takes two bad drivers to have an accident, okay?
你告诉令妹， 拿起你的电话给我打电话。
Okay-
Listen, tell your sister to pick up her phone or call me back or something.
- 好了，我的朋友。玩的很开心。 - 再见了，爸爸。
Okay. All right, buddy.
You have a good one. Bye,Dad.
借此你姐姐。 把它放在卡车上。
Hey, honey, take this to your sister.
Throw it in the truck, okay?
Okay, I will.
- 在哪里希娜睡觉 - 与她的朋友艾米丽。
So where is Sheena staying?
At her friend Emily's.
- 是否艾米莉 - 是的！
Is Emily a real person?
这是第三年。 他有他自己的公寓。
Yeah.
Yeah, she's a sophomore. She has an apartment.
这是紧急情况。 不花钱的话，我想回去。
Okay, this is in case of emergency.
Don't spend it, I want it back.
谢谢。
Okay. Thanks.
你做你的功课
Did you do your homework?
几乎所有的东西，但我会完成的明天。
Most of it, but I can finish tomorrow night.
大三的时候很 重要的UNI。不要搞砸了。
Honey, 11th grade is really important for college. Don't blow it.
我知道，我知道。 这就是我们要的UT。
I know, I know. I mean, we're going to UT and everything.
你难道不想去吗 “希娜，是什么 与妈妈“之旅承兑汽油。
Oh, don't you want me to come?
"Come on, Sheena, road trip with Mom!" I'll pay for gas.
Fine.
我在开玩笑。我有工作。
Just kidding. I have work.
- 叫我当你到达那里。 - 我会做。
Call me when you get there.
I will.
玩得开心！
Have fun!
听起来好像一个愿景 都非常简单。
That sounds to me like just another
extreme Mason view of everything.
一点也不。最后，我得到了它。
Not at all! I finally figured it out.
当他们意识到 这将是太贵了,,,
It's like when they realized it was gonna be too expensive
建立半机器人和机器人，
to actually build cyborgs and robots.
还是在成本 飞涨，他们决定人类,,,
I mean, the costs of that were impossible.
They decided to just let humans
自我改造成机器人。
turn themselves into robots.
- 这是发生了什么。 - 现在
That's what's going on right now.
为什么不呢有几十亿 我们在那里，什么都不做。
Oh, right now?
Yeah! I mean, why not?
They're billions of us just laying around, not really doing anything.
我们已经花费。 直到我们自我维护，
We don't cost anything.
We're even pretty good at self-maintenance and reproducing constantly.
我们不断重现。
And as it turns out, we're already biologically programmed
正如我们所看到的，我们,,,
生物程序 成为半机器人。
for our little cyborg upgrades.
- 作为 - 认真。
How? Seriously.
我读到一篇文章，有一天说,,,
I read this thing the other day about how...
当我们听到的声音 收件箱
When you hear that ding on your inbox,
接受注射 多巴胺在大脑。
you get like a dopamine rush in your brain.
好像我们化学奖励 为让它得到洗脑。
It's like we're being chemically rewarded
for allowing ourselves to be brainwashed.
这不为恶我们搞砸了！
How evil is that? We're fucked.
你以为删除您 Facebook的页面会改变什么
So you deleting your Facebook page is gonna change all that?
我记得当它做TRAVER 去年。每个人都嘲笑他。
Remember when Trevor deleted his Facebook page last year
你笑起来比任何人。
and everyone just hated him?
我一直在笑TRAVER。
You made more fun of him than anyone.
I still make fun of Trevor though.
你需要注意的是可悲的。
It was like he was so pathetically desperate for attention.
或者是不同的，什么的。
Or to be different, or something.
并将其与愚蠢的故事结束 它在学校的报纸。
That's just 'cause they did that lame story about it in the school paper.
我不得不做出一个伟大的 广告，当他回到在随后的一个月。
And then he had to make a big announcement about it
when he came back a month later.
但我不在乎。
That's the thing, though, I'm not doing it for attention.
我想试住 我的生活中没有的画面。
I just wanna try and not live my life through a screen.
我想一个真正的互动。
I want some kind of actual interaction.
一个真正的人。 任何资料在网上公布。
A real person, not just the profile they put up.
道歉。你到底在说什么
Oh, I'm sorry. Were you saying something?
没关系。 我知道你在开玩笑，但,,,
Yeah, okay, I know you're joking.
有一定的道理。您 国家与手机的整个行程。
But, I mean, it's kind of true.
You have been, you know, checking your phone this whole time,
你做什么工作什么呢
so, what're you really doing?
如果你不关心他们做什么 上周六下午，朋友，
You don't care what your friends are up to on a Saturday afternoon,
你不是沉浸 我深深的委屈，
but you're also obviously not fully experiencing my profound bitching.
它似乎所有 他们是介于两者之间的地方。
So, yeah, it's like everyone's just stuck in like an in-between state.
如果没有经历严重的事情。
Not really experiencing anything.
它不是一个经验。
It's not an experience, it's just information.
米拉。例如:
Look. For example,
我得到的地址 俱乐部，在那里我们见面。
I just got the address of the club where we're meeting them later,
因此，我们不丧失 甸街道后。
so we won't be wandering the streets of Austin lost for an hour tonight.
非常感谢你，Facebook的。
Thank you very much, Facebook.
我发了条给我妈。
And then I just texted my mom back.
革命！
Oh, that's groundbreaking.
你有没有看到你55分钟。
She hasn't seen you in, like, 55 minutes?
天啊！最重要,,,
Oh...
Oh, my God, most importantly,
我被告知， 我们有一个小型猪。
Meg's family just got a miniature pet pig.
你说得对。这是,,, 这是一个非常可爱的小猪。
Okay, you're right. That is a really cute, tiny pig.
我们的生活可以继续。
Our lives can go on.
我想要一个。
I want one.
好球。
Nice shot.
他出示了1 识别并通过。
Yeah, just give the lady at the front y'all's IDs
and,uh, she should let you in.
206室，对不对
It's Room 206, right? Awesome. Mmm.
- 但不要在那里过夜。 - 好吧。玩得开心。
It's not weird that we're staying there, is it?
No, it's fine. Have fun.
谢谢。
Thank you.
多久你一起出去吗
How long have you guys been dating?
大约三个月。
About three months.
我们遇到了在一个聚会上都不错。
Yeah, we met at a party and it's been chill.
- 这似乎安静。 - 是的，就是这样。
Yeah, he seems cool. Yeah, he is.
- 它也去得克萨斯大学 - 是的。
- Does he go to UT, too? - Yeah.
你在学什么
What does he study?
历史和意大利,,, 作为二级学科。
He's studying history and Italian, I think, his minor, yeah.
想教
Does he wanna teach Italian?
我不知道。我认为他仍然想着。
I think he's still figuring stuff out.
他已经决定了。他很聪明。
Yeah. He'll figure it out.
He's smart. Smart, yeah.
和你住的地方，当你来到这里
So, where are you thinking about living when you come here?
我不知道。 我们将着眼于公寓,,,
Um, I'm not really sure yet.
We're gonna look at apartments tomorrow.
晨。
Um...
我的父母认为 我住在大学宿舍。
But I know my parents sort of were expecting me to live in a dorm.
不过，我将支付单，所以,,,
But I'm paying my way through college,
不那么重要了。
so it doesn't really matter that much.
你不必听什么 18后告诉你的父母。
You don't have to listen to your parents after you turn 18.
特别是，如果你不帮经济。
Especially if they're not helping you financially.
这就是我的想法。
That's what I figured.
卧室也不错。 尤其是当它们混合。
But living in a dorm isn't so bad. Yeah?
I mean, especially if it's a coed dorm.
我从来没有过 周围有那么多的帅哥。
Yeah.
I mean, I've never been around so many cute guys at once.
UNI是乐趣！
Like, college is really fun.
- 我很兴奋。 - 这是很好的，是的。
I'm excited. It's great, yeah.
Oh.
在我出生那天我就开始年龄
没有人告诉我，生命 我能够这么寂寞和残忍
他在23有灰白的头发
这样的生活 运气不好会跟我结束
老黑乌鸦 槽已经离开我的脸
而在旅途中 我在同一个地方
艰苦的生活会跟我结束
施工过程中的最新死亡 胡佛水坝是他的儿子，
The last death at the Hoover Dam construction site
was his son, Patrick Tierney,
帕特里克・蒂尔尼， 谁死在1935年12月20日。
who died on December 20th, 1935,
短短13年后。
exactly 13 years to the day.
你看到了女孩的姐妹
See those sorority girls over there?
我已经决定了。如果您删除 Facebook的页面，我会推出我的。
I've just decided,
if you delete your Facebook page, I'm pledging.
是的，在几年 这将是你,,,,,,那将是我的。
Yeah, in just a few years that's you,
and that's gonna be me.
...Inlaid into the terrazzo floors was a star map,
星图。一个地图 天体的准确,,,
a celestial map of heavenly bodies so accurately displayed
可能绘制的位置 北极星14000年后,,,
that one could chart the procession of the pole star
14,000 years into the future, such that future generations upon...
和后代,,,
I wonder what his deal is.
我不知道它做什么。 不来吃饭。
I mean, he obviously has money to eat here.
是的。他是在UT教授。 并与后投保。
He just said. He's a UT professor, tenure and everything.
看看所有这些人。 你为什么在这里凌晨三点
Look at all these people.
What're they even doing here at 3:00 in the morning?
我们做什么 在凌晨三点
What are we even doing here at 3:00 in the morning?
你知道为什么我们在这里
We know what we're doing here.
奶酪！我们有一个目的。
Queso. We have a purpose.
右。
Hell, yeah.
在明年夏天， 等会我们的生活。
You know, by next summer, this'll just be our lives.
Mmm.
熬夜。视图显示。
Staying out all night, going to shows, whatever we want.
我们想要的东西。
We ever gonna go to class?
你还课
Sometimes.
- 几乎每。 - 听起来不错。
When it feels right. When the inspiration hits.
- 直到灵感闪现。 - 仅在所述时间。
Only then.
- 还要别的吗 - 更多的奶酪
Anything else?
Uh, more queso? Yeah.
- 神,,, - 什么
Jesus.
是不是有点势不可挡
What?
I don't know, doesn't it all seem a little overwhelming?
这所大学,,,,,,
I mean, college?
我喜欢这个主意 远离家乡，和,,,
I mean, I like the idea of being away from home
获取知识 并提高我的照片，但它是,,,
and gaining skills and getting better at photography.
我不认为这是 变革。
I just...
I don't know, I'm not counting on it
being some big, transformative experience.
不要认为这是为变革。 这只是在下一个步骤。
I don't think it's that transformative.
I just see it as the next step.
这就像一个预先设定的空间 你已经有你的姓名和电话号码。
But it's like a preordained slot
that's already got your name and number on it.
不要以为这是关键到我的未来。
I don't think it's the key to my future.
看看我的妈妈。
'Cause, I mean, look at my mom.
他毕业后找到了一份工作。
She got her degree and got a pretty good job.
- 支付帐单,,, - 我喜欢你的妈妈。
She can pay her bills.
I like your mom.
我也是，但我的意思是,,,
I like my mom, too. I just mean...
在背景中， 她的困惑我。
Basically she's still just as fuckin' confused as I am.
谢谢。
Thank you. Thanks.
喂
- Hello? - Hey.
嗨！呵呵,,,
Um...
不是山姆告诉你 我们,,,我们会在这里
Did Sam tell you we were gonna stay here?
号
No.
对不起，呃,,,
Sorry. Um...
我们说你会,,,,,, 出去度周末。
She said you were out of town for the weekend.
我是。我刚回来。
Yeah, I was. I just got back.
你是她,,,哥哥吗
Are you her brother?
是的，我,,,,,,我是一个梅森。
Yeah, I'm Mason.
她是希娜。
Um, this is Sheena.
Hello. Uh, great.
有什么好。
All right. I'm gonna leave my stuff here, if it's okay,
好吧。我将离开我 的东西，我要去吃点东西,,,
and get something to eat.
- 我会回来的一段时间。 - 我们必须去很快,,,
I'll just come back in a little bit?
Yeah, yeah, we have to get out of here soon anyway.
所以,,,
All right. It's nice meeting you.
- 好吧。很高兴认识你。 - 同样在这里。
- Yeah. You, too. - Sorry!
对不起！
它是如此的难受！
- That was so awkward. Mmm-hmm.
梅森！冠军银牌。
Mason, silver-medal winner.
- 恭喜！ - 谢谢。
Congratulations!
- 我发现了关于奖学金。 - 是所有有所帮助,,
Thank you.
Heard you got a scholarship. Yeah.
当你去到那里
Yeah, every little bit helps, you know.
在这个夏天，我想。
Yeah. When you gonna go out there?
End of the summer, I think.
我将努力早一点。 我想节省一些钱。
Work some more before then, try to save up some money, at least.
之前，你必须凑合。
Yeah, before you have to fend for yourself. Yeah.
这就是这个想法。
Yeah, that's the idea.
你感觉如何
Well, how are you feeling about it?
兴奋。 一半兴奋，一半害怕。
Excited, you know.
But kind of half-excited, half-terrified.
- 这妖娆的恐慌。 - 这是正确的。
Yeah, kind of that voluptuous panic.
这将是很好的。这将是伟大的为您服务。
Yeah. Exactly.
Well, it's gonna be good. It's gonna be crazy good.
对我来说，我喜欢单 比高中得多。
I liked college a lot better than high school.
找到你自己 人们在UNI，你知道吗
You kinda find your people in college, you know?
这是正确的。
Exactly.
你会没事的。有一个好 心脏。听你的心脏。
You'll be fine.
You got a good heart, just follow your heart. Yeah?
- 谢谢。 - 祝好运。不要忘了用牙线。
Thanks. Good luck.
Don't forget to floss.
- 你看，三种。什么 - 我不能，明天见。
I just don't get why you're being so fucking childish.
我不明白为什么 你表现得像个孩子。
I'm not being childish!
事实并非如此。你成为了一个 有大事要告诉大家。
You're the one who made it into this big thing by telling everyone!
我没有告诉任何人。
I haven't told anyone.
你怎么知道Cynthy 你去参加派对了一个失败者，
So Cynthia just magically knows
尽管没有看到他
you're going to the prom with this loser,
even though you're not dating him anymore?
- 他是我最好的朋友。 - 你最好的朋友有一个大嘴巴。
She's my best friend.
Well, your best friend has a big fucking mouth.
与她商量一下，然后。
Take it up with her, then.
你为什么不告诉 这是罗伯特・托什
Why don't you just tell Miss Fuckin' Rubber Jaw
您可以继续谈判，
she can keep on talking,
而包括真相
as long as she includes the truth,
这是不 本来这次谈话,,,
which is that we wouldn't be having this conversation
如果你的男朋友是不是单 超出这个周末。
if your college boyfriend weren't out of town this weekend.
你已经买了票。
You had already bought the tickets.
不要紧。 我只是想表示友好。
It's just prom, it's not like it matters.
I'm just trying to be friends with you.
这是一个耻辱。我不能做到这一点。
It's just humiliating. I can't do that.
先生:“我不关心 别人怎么想我的。 “
Mister I-Don't-Care- What-Anyone-Else- Thinks-Of-Me.
他妈的说。我在乎的是什么 我觉得对我来说，这没什么大不了的。
Fuck anyone else!
I care what I think of me, which isn't much right now.
可惜了党的国王。
King of the Pity Prom.
好了，我们不会。
Fine. We're not going.
太棒了。
Great.
我们是什么,,,
Why are we even...
我们知道这是未来。 我是一个谁做了这件事的东西。
I mean, we both knew this was coming.
I'm just the one who did something about it.
- 是的，你从性交单的家伙。 - 你他妈的！
Yeah, fucking some college guy.
Oh, fuck you!
- 我不后悔任何事情。 - 当然不是。
I don't regret anything.
Of course you don't.
这是一种解脱，是与人 谁没有按下的所有时间。
You know, it's actually kind of a relief
not to have to be around someone who's so gloomy all the time.
世界上没有那么可怕。 并非一切都是一个很大的阴谋。
The world's not so horrible.
Not everything's some big conspiracy against humanity.
我很高兴你能这么想。
It's great that you can think that way.
当然约会运动员 可以帮助你,,,,,,清除你的头脑。
You know, I'm sure dating a jock really helps to clear the mind.
这不是一个运动员。 只有在曲棍球队。
He's not a jock, okay? He just happens to be on the lacrosse team.
我们将在大学 不同的明年。
We're all going to other schools next year anyway.
它不是这样一个严肃的关系。
It's not some super-serious relationship.
太好了！现在我感觉好多了。
Oh, great. I feel so much better now.
- 我想有乐趣。 - 一个好他传球。
We're just having fun.
I bet he's having fun.
马都拉，梅森。
Grow up, Mason.
我不是一个人了。
It's not like I haven't been with anyone else.
谁
Who?
你在乎什么
What do you care?
- 是谁 - 谁在乎
Who?
Does it matter?
您提出来的。
You're the one who brought it up.
这是没有意义的。
This is pointless.
现在，你正在玩的傻瓜。
Now you're just trying to be an asshole.
他妈的！我宁愿 把我的球,,,
Holy crap, I would rather have my balls clawed off
而不必 再忍受这样的事情。
than ever sit through anything like that ever again.
- 嗯，从来没有碰我们。 - 感谢上帝。
Well, you never, ever have to.
Oh, my God, thank you.
- 给我。 - 所有你。喝了这一切。
Give me that. Dude, it's all you.
Drink up.
你今晚跟我出去吗 有很有趣的事情。
So you coming out with me tonight, brother?
Should be some pretty awesome stuff happening.
我要去看秀 我的父亲在奥斯汀。
Naw, dude, I'm going to this show with my dad in Austin.
一些朋友一起玩。
His friend's playing.
好了，有乐趣。
Have fun with that, I guess.
他妈的！有两辆车。
Fuck, there are so many cars here. I don't wanna go in there!
我不想进入。
Dude, you will have so much fun.
男人，你俩有乐趣。 你的家人爱你。
Your family loves you! Have a swell time.
传递得非常好。
Fuck you. You're coming in with me.
- 你跟我来。 - 不，不，地狱，没有。 - 是的！
Oh, no. Shit, no. Yes.
我妈妈是爱你的。你打个招呼。
Yes, you are. My mom loves you. You have to say hi.
想得罪
Do you want to hurt her feelings? Mmm-mmm.
好吧来吧！
Well, then, let's go get 'em!
一秒钟。只需一秒钟，真的。
Just for a second. Just a second, seriously.
- 你在敌人的领土。 - 我们已经知道了。
You know, you're in sort of enemy territory here.
We're aware.
看看谁在这里！
Look who's here!
Hey!
Get a job!
等待，等待。我们将采取的照片。
Congratulations!
No, no, no! Wait. We're gonna take pictures.
Put it back on.
有一个摄像头
Can you get a camera?
恭喜你，宝贝。 我不认识你，但我向你表示祝贺。
Congratulations, baby.
I don't know you, but congratulations!
很好。看这里。
All right, look here.
- 微笑！ - 准备好了！
Smile. Here we go.
这是很好的。
Oh, that's a good one.
And good. Got it.
山姆，你在哪里萨曼莎！
We need... Sam, where are you?
- Samantha! - Sam.
和梅森的父亲吗 我很慷慨的，到这里来。
And where's Mason Senior?
I'm feeling generous. Come here.
Great. And beautiful!
漂亮！
I'll email these to everyone.
他们会发送电子邮件。
Don't even start. Don't start, don't start.
不启动。不启动。
这似乎令人难以置信的是已经 到目前为止。我很感谢。
Can't believe you guys came all this way. It means a lot to me.
我们不会错过任何东西 世界。我为你感到骄傲。
Mmm...
We wouldn't have missed it for anything!
I'm so proud of you. Congratulations.
恭喜您！
I'm really sorry that Lee couldn't be here. He's on his senior trip.
我很遗憾，李进不来。 这是毕业旅行。
No, tell him I said hi. I will.
- 发送问候。 - 我会做。
Abby, I didn't even recognize you. How old are you now?
艾比，我不认识。 你几岁了
I'm 13.
- 十三。 - 令人难以置信。
Wow.
的填充！
All right, let's top her off.
- 你会 - 是的，当然。
You want some, doll?
Um, sure, whatever. Yeah.
我给你的东西。
I got you something.
它是什么
What is it?
这是一个储蓄债券。它具有其值。
That is a savings bond. That is worth something.
这是比金钱更好， 你花钱。
It's better than money. You'd just spend that.
- 围棋，是你妈妈 - 是的，她是。
God, is that your mom?
Yeah. Yeah. That's her. Wow.
规则三秒钟。 把它放在盘子上。
Three-second rule. Put it on your plate.
Such a good dad. Really.
我想敬酒梅森！
I know. I'm trying to help.
Come here, you guys. I want to make a little toast to Mason.
梅森，我不知道 想要一个党今晚，但是,,,
Now, Mason, I know you didn't really want to have a party today,
我们做的。
but We did.
只是完成 在生活中学一次！
And you only graduate high school once in your life.
我想festejarte， 庆祝下一阶段,,,
So I want to celebrate you and this next phase.
您将学习两种 大学。你会笑的这么多。
And you're gonna learn so much in college,
有老师谁启发你。
you're gonna have so much fun.
You're gonna have inspiring teachers,
你会学到更多的艺术品。
you're gonna learn more about your art.
我爱你。我为你感到骄傲。
I love you, babe. So proud of you.
- 梅森。 - 梅森！
- To Mason. - To Mason!
- To Mason. - Here, here!
倒是你，兄弟。
All right, you're up, kid.
Oh, uh...
当然，嗯,,,嗯,,,
All right, uh... Well, Mason, I'll make a toast to the future.
梅森，举杯 由,,,未来。对于你的未来。
To your future.
它已经难以 这,,,,,,到底学年。
You know, it's been a little sketchy
想知道你选择什么样的大学。
this end of the school year here,
trying to figure out what school to go to.
梅森表示，他希望,,,
Mason told me that he wanted
是因为离家远越好，
to get as far away from home as possible,
同时保持协议 留在状态。
but still honor our agreement that we pay in-state tuition,
我对此表示赞赏。
which I do appreciate.
这是一个聪明的人 并且将有一个伟大的未来。
He's a prudent man and, uh, he's gonna have a great future.
为了您的健康，朋友。
So here's to you, buddy.
To the future!
Congratulations!
儿子梅森！
Mason Junior! High school graduate, 18 and straight!
刚毕业，18和杂！
我不理它。
Just ignore him. My brother needs to learn to pace himself.
我的哥哥的需求 学会控制。
I've not known you as long as everybody here,
我不知道你们俩 因为其他人在这里。
但因为你 ímet've成长了很多。
but since I have known you, you've grown a lot and I'm proud of you.
我为你感到骄傲。
So, if this photography thing doesn't work out,
如果拍摄不工作，
you know you always got a job.
总有一份工作 - 没有箍。
Lose that earring. But...
也许你可以找到 在接收部分。为了您的健康！
Uh, you know, maybe I can get you front of house.
All right. To you, buddy!
山姆，一个字！
Sam, say something!
来吧，萨姆。
Come on, Samantha. Um...
来吧，宝贝！
Come on, darling.
祝好运！
Good luck.
Aw...
- 所以你分手的女朋友吗 - 是的，最近。
So you broke up with your girlfriend?
Yeah, yeah, just recently.
- 他叫什么名字 - 希娜。
What was her name?
希娜。你去上大学
Sheena.
She's gonna go to college with you?
不，不,,,,,,留,,,,,, 在德克萨斯州的这一边。
No. No?
Hmm. She's staying in this part of Texas.
你需要一个骑单
Okay-
You need a ride to college?
我想打个招呼 才离开。
I just wanted to say hello before you got out of here.
是已知的，不是吗，安妮
You guys met before, haven't you? Annie, Aunt Jen?
- 是的，山姆,,,,,,毕业。 - 右。
Yeah, we met at, uh...
而其中的小家伙
Sam's graduation. Oh, yeah.
And with your little one. Where is he?
他留在家里。
Oh, he's at home.
他很不高兴，在山姆。
Remember? He was such a pain in Sam's thing that...
我很想看看吧！
I would love to see him.
我们预计 特殊的周末，和,,,
We have a special weekend this weekend, so...
我很高兴你满足。
I'm so glad you found her, I really am.
你见过他的一个好时机，我想。
You've got him at a good time, I think.
我想是这样。
I think so, too. Yeah.
- 很高兴见到你。 - 我也是。
It's good to see you two.
- 我是你的儿子感到自豪。 - 我们都是。
Nice to see you, too,Jen.
So proud of your boy.
Yeah. Yeah, we all are.
她是个女巫！
She's a bitch and a half.
你记得要去UNI，你知道吗
You got to remember, you're going
如果你看 东西我还是你的父亲，
to college, though, all right?
And if you're anything like me or your old man,
你去了几个女人。
you're gonna be pulling down some serious wool.
你会跟着腔内的窜动。
You're gonna be tapping some masterful gap.
您将行使紧随其后。
You're gonna be doing some good work out there.
想想吧。有许多鲜花在这个花束。
Think about it. Awful lot of flowers in that bouquet.
但是，帮我一个忙。
But you got to do me a favor.
这个夏天你会 处于弱势地位。
You're going to be vulnerable this summer, all right?
在性爱分离保护自己。
Remember to use protection during breakup sex.
他知道我在说什么。
This guy knows exactly of which I speak.
是什么发生在他身上。瞧！
Look what happened to him. Voila'.
史蒂芬,,,
Steven.
健康。
Cheers.
- 这不是那么简单。 - 四年！
It's not that simple.
Four more years. Four more years.
I'm just saying.
- 回收 - 有一个包在那里。
Do y'all recycle? Should I...
I have one started there.
Oh, yeah, right. Great.
我是你唯一的前夫在派对
Am I your only ex at this party?
是的。
Yes. I'm not your only wife here, though.
不过，我在这里不是你唯一的妻子。
Yeah.
你能相信，这两个 完成学业
Can you believe they're both out of high school?
号
No. No, I can't.
我不能。
You did a great job with both of them, by the way.
你已经做了伟大的工作既。
谢谢你这么说。
Thanks for saying that.
我从来没有想过我会听你说。
I never thought I'd hear you say that.
这是事实。谢谢。
Well, it's true.
Thank you.
- 你再这样做。 - 我知道，我知道。
You're doing it all over again, huh?
I know, I know, right?
缺少15年 具有,,,,,,空巢。
It's gonna be 15 years till I have an empty nest.
我喜欢帮助。
Hmm.
But I'd love to pitch in, help with this, if I could.
为了解决这个问题。 这是非常好的，你所做的一切。
I mean, it's so great that you did this.
我只是想给你一点,,,,,,
Can I just give you a little?
- 如果我可以帮助。 - 当然，当然。
I'd appreciate it if I could.
Sure. Yeah.
我没有现金。
But l don't have any cash.
这是在安妮的投资组合。马上回来。
Oh, I know, it's in Annie's purse. I'll be right back.
强悍。这家伙是玩家 曲棍球单。你能做些什么
So it sucks. I mean, the guy's a college lacrosse player.
What are you gonna do?
她也不喜欢运动。
She didn't even like sports.
- 啤酒 - 不，谢谢。
You want a beer?
- 你可以喝。 - 不，谢谢。
No, that's all right.
You can have one. It's okay.
所有发生在我们身上 同样在这种或那种方式。
Yeah, well, for what it's worth,
we've all been through the exact same thing at one point or another.
这是不一样的。 你永远不知道好。
It's not the same, though. I mean, you never got to know her.
我知道这是不一样的。
No, I know, I know. It's not the same.
我不知道我做错了什么。
I just don't know what I did wrong.
嗨，吉米！你好。
Hey, Jimmy. Hey, man.
你好，梅森。
Hey. Hey, Mason.
我们正在追捕中 绿色客房，有问题吗
We're up here raiding the green room. Hope that's okay.
所有的10分。
That's totally cool.
All right.
是MJ
Wow! Is that MJ?
Uh-huh, right?
令人难以置信的。
Unbelievable.
我们决定早点来见你。
Well, we just decided to come a little early, check you out.
期限和将与您一段时间。
That's cool man, let me finish up. I'll be up in a minute.
我保证你没有做错任何事情。
All right. I guarantee you, you didn't do anything wrong.
那些爱 二次行不通。
These high school love things, they never work out.
Here, come here.
都是 在变化如此之快，你知道吗
I mean, everybody's just changing so much, you know?
赔率是两个年轻 留在相同的波长是,,,
The odds of two young people staying on the same wavelength are...
- 是的，但是,,,,,, - 我也保证,,,
Yeah, but still... Look, and I also guarantee you
你生活的每一天 你花哭了个傻丫头,,,,,,
that every day of your life
that you spend crying over some silly girl
这是在浪费时间。
is a complete waste of time.
但是，这不是一个傻丫头。
She wasn't a silly girl, though.
这是一个严肃的人。 我真的以为,,,
I mean, she's a serious person.
And I really thought we were...
什么
What?
我不知道。
I don't know.
事实是， 女人永远不会满足。
Here's the truth. Women are never satisfied,okay?
他们总是 找赎模式。
They're always looking to potentially trade up,
很抱歉，但 就是发生在你身上，伟大的朋友。
and that's, I'm sorry to say,
what I think has happened to you, my fine-feathered friend.
这意味着什么
What does that even mean?
这意味着，你给不 控制你的自尊希拉的。
It means don't hand over the controls to your self-esteem to Sheila.
希娜。
Sheena. All right.
这意味着你有责任 你自己。不是你的女朋友，你的妈妈，还是我。
It means you are responsible for you,
not your girlfriend, not your mom, not me, you.
您。如果你真的 你要好好照顾自己,,,,,,
And if you truly take care of you,
你会惊讶有多少女孩 希娜的敲你的门。
you will be amazed at how much girls like Sheena
start lining up at your front door.
大。
Great.
你必须找到一种方法 你从包中分离出来。
You just gotta separate yourself from the pack in some way.
你擅长什么，你知道吗
Excel at something, you know, and then you have your pick of the litter
在那里你可以选择你想要的 牛群当你前进,,,
when the front-runner hussies start sniffing around.
开始嗅探。
So what you're saying is I should take up lacrosse.
所以我应该献身于曲棍球。
Exactly.
右。
Or you could, you know, start a band.
,,,,,,形成一个摇滚乐队。
Worked for me a long time ago. I think it's still working for Jimmy.
它早就为我工作
它仍然起作用吉米。
Or you just keep taking pictures.
还在拍照。
She hated the pictures I took of her.
她恨我把他的照片。
I'm sick to death of her, okay?
我烦死了。
I only met her a few times, and yes, she was cute, all right,
我只看到一对夫妇 时间，是的，它很可爱。
但事实上， 我一直认为这是一个有点,,,
but truth be told, I always thought she was a little bit...
有点无聊你。
You know, a little bit too square for you.
它们不是在同一波长。
You know, not quite the same vibe.
你知道发生了什么给我
You really thought that?
他是在一个较低的水平。
On some subtle, lower level.
I mean, I wasn't surprised
我并不感到惊讶， 有兴趣的曲棍球婴儿。
when it turned out she was interested in some Knucklehead lacrosse player, okay?
基本上，这一切都取决于 时间在这些事情上。
I mean, bottom line is, it's all timing with these things, you know.
看看我和你妈妈。
I mean, take your mom and me.
我想我已经成为,,,
I think I probably turned into the boring,
镗绝育 她想15-20年前。
castrated guy she wanted me to be
15, 20 years ago, you know?
我不是说他错了会生气的。
I'm not saying she was wrong to be pissed, I'm not.
我只是说，它可以 已经有点耐心。
I'm just saying that she could've been
多一点宽容。
a little more patient, little more forgiving.
我会救 醉酒白痴的游行。
Would've saved me that parade of drunken assholes.
有什么意义
So, what's the point?
什么
Of What?
我不知道。这。一切。
I don't know, any of this. Everything.
一切吗
Everything? What's the point?
有什么意义 什么他妈的我知道吗
I mean, I sure as shit don't know.
没有一个知道这是为什么。全部,,,
Neither does anybody else, okay?
即兴发挥，你知道吗 好事是，你觉得东西。
We're all just winging it, you know?
The good news is you're feeling stuff.
你必须坚持这一点。
And you've got to hold on to that.
你长大了，不觉得多。 皮肤变得坚硬。
You do. I mean, you get older and you don't feel as much.
Your skin gets tougher.
你的感觉是对的照片。
The point is those pictures you took,
他们把照片 全州，你赢了。
thousands of submissions from all over the state, and you won.
我赢得了银牌。
Well, I got silver.
与人相处。
And nine other people did, too. I'm gonna kill you.
我想说的是，我相信你，梅森。
I'm trying to tell you that I believe in you, Mason.
我觉得你很特别。如果你 女孩看不出来，他妈的。
I think you're really special,
and if some girl doesn't see that, then fuck her, you know.
这个问题是专门 一个年轻的礼物。
Hey, this next one of 'em goes out to a young man in the house.
我见到他时，我还是个孩子。
Whoo-hoo! Known him since he was just a small boy.
现在学完了 二，让我觉得自己老了。
Now he's all graduated from high school and making me feel old.
你毕业了，梅森。
Happy high school graduation, Mason.
谢谢。
Thank you.
打抱不平。 将有四大类。
Okay, guys, let's be clear. We're gonna break this into four categories.
A:有什么 谁想要随身携带的童年。
One, anything you want to keep from your childhood
and you're taking with you.
二:观光拍摄。
Two, throwing away. Three, donating.
三:观光捐赠。
And four, whatever you want to try to sell
四:我们想尝试什么 卖在展会这个周末。
at the garage sale next weekend,
什么是不卖将捐献。
whatever we don't sell, we're donating.
请问公寓没有 阁楼，储藏的东西
Doesn't the apartment have like an attic, or storage or something?
不，你不明白。
No. You're missing the point.
我们不会采取废话 老我的小公寓。
We're not gonna drag a bunch of crap to Mom's tiny apartment.
另一个举动，简直不敢相信。
Can't believe we're moving again.
我谨动议。你喜欢在两年前提出的。 在奥斯汀的一间公寓。
No, I'm moving.
You moved two years ago. You have an apartment in Austin.
梅森移动在秋季。
Mason is moving in the fall.
我完成了！
I'm done.
这将是巨大的。我有很多选择。 我，我可以采取休假。
This'll be great for me. I'll have all these options.
I could take a sabbatical.
我可以献身于写作。 获取出版了我。
I could get some writing done, try to get published.
什么圣诞节 我们该怎么办
What about Christmas, though? What are we gonna do?
我不会共用一个房间跟他。
I'm not sharing a room with him.
其中，你会睡在沙发上。 我们将使用充气垫。
One of you will sleep on the couch,
and we'll use that blow-up mattress.
而如何洗我的衣服吗
How am I supposed to do my laundry?
我给人一种 轻推离巢。
Sam, I'm gently pushing you out of the nest.
也许奇迹般地下降 找一些硬币,,,
And on your way down, you may magically find some quarters
洗衣服 在自己的公寓。
that you use to do laundry in your own apartment.
但请！你是,,,大人。
Come on! You guys are adults!
他们必须承担责任。
You need to take some responsibility. Now, what do you want?
他们想要什么
I'm gonna get the veggie burger.
í的素食汉堡。
I'm not having anything, not hungry.
没有我。我不饿。
What's wrong with you?
怎么了
I'm sick.
我心情不好。
What is it, your head? Do you have a fever?
你有什么请问头你有没有发烧
She's pregnant.
你怀孕了。
No. To be honest, I drank way too much last night.
事实上，我喝多了昨晚。
You weren't driving, were you? No, no.
- 有开车，对不对 - 不，不。
Cary's back home, too, and we just hung out.
嘉莉又回来了。 在共同度过。
You know, peach Smirnoff s, they just go down so easy.
- 杰克丹尼尔下来喝了点酒,,, - 不，不。
No, no. Hey, that's not an excuse.
没有任何借口。
You can still pack boxes.
就像你可以填写框。人 要移动尽可能快。
These people want to move in as soon as possible.
你好。
Hi, guys. I'm Ernesto, how are you?
Ernesto'm Larrio。
You probably don't remember me,
她不记得我，但是,,,
but I worked on your septic line years ago.
我管了几年前。
Oh, yeah.
右。
Believe it or not, you changed my life.
不管你信不信，它改变了我的生活。
You told me that day that I was smart
我说我是 智能化，不得不去单。
and that I should go to school.
我把他的意见。
I took your advice. I signed up for English classes,
先用英语班。
and then a year later, I went to community college
一年后，我上了大学 社区和管理的大专学历。
and I got my Associates degree,
现在，我在UNI 执照后的状态。
and I'm working on my bachelor's now at Texas State.
我在这里有一个经理。
And also one of the managers here.
辣妹！
That's great.
很高兴看到它，并有 这个机会向他们表示感谢。
It's good to see you, because I really wanted
a chance to thank you for that.
这是一个大问题，对我来说。
Gracias. It really meant a lot to me.
午餐是在我身上。
Don't worry about lunch. It's on me. It's the least I can do.
- 这是我至少可以做到。 - 谢谢。
You guys should listen to her. She's a smart lady.
让她如此。这是一个聪明的女人。
谢谢。
Thank you.
是不是疯了 计算机知道你是谁,,,
Isn't that kind of crazy, though,
that a computer knows who you are
20题在窗体上。
from just 20 questions off a form?
似乎有只 世界各地的八类人。
I guess there are really only like eight types of people in the world.
有子集 由于男性和女性，但是,,,
I mean, there are subsets like male and female,
显然，我们不 作为独一无二的，因为我们的想法。
but apparently we're not as unique as we want to think we are.
你有没有跟他谈过
Have you even talked to this guy yet?
没有，但我们交换的消息。
No, but we've been trading emails. He seems pretty cool.
它看起来不错。文学研究,,,
He's studying literature and anthropology
和人类学，并爱 明亮的眼睛，这是一件好事。
and he's way into Bright Eyes, so that's not so bad.
他告诉我说,,,
But, anyways, he was telling me about how
该系统分配对等体 卧室给人有点吓人。
the system they use for assigning roommates is kinda spooky.
书呆子的满意率 与以前是60％对等体。
The freshman satisfaction rate for new roommates used to be like 60%,
而现在是100％。
and now it's 100, just 'cause of the computer.
仅由计算机。
Well, sounds like he'll be a good roommate, then.
这将是一个很好的伴侣，那么。
Yeah. But we pretty much decided
但是，我们得出这样的结论,,,,,,
that soon they won't even need a questionnaire
很快就不用了问卷。
'cause they'll just let the NSA scan your digital ghost
美国国家安全局会扫描 数码鬼,,,
and they'll tell you who your roommate is
他们会告诉你，谁是你的合作伙伴，
based on everything you've ever said, written or clicked.
基于一切 曾经说，写，或者你点击。
你把它放在了吗
Did you put this in here again?
我不想。
I don't want it.
来吧！这是你的第一张照片。
Come on, it's the first picture you ever took.
正因如此，我走了，对不对
All the more reason to leave it behind, right?
- 这是怎么回事 - 没有！
What? Nothing.
妈的，什么是错的
No, what is it? It's nothing!
什么都没有！
Mom.
妈妈,,,
这是我一生中最糟糕的一天！
This is the worst day of my life.
你在说什么
What're you talking about?
我知道这一天会到来。
I knew this day was coming.
我无法想象 你会很高兴吧！
I didn't know you were gonna be
so fuckin' happy to be leaving.
这并不是说我太高兴了。 你是怎么想到
I mean, it's not that I'm that happy. What do you expect?
你知道我在想什么 我的人生就是这样！
You know what I'm realizing? My life is just gonna go, like that.
这些生命的里程碑。
This series of milestones.
结婚，生子，离婚。
Getting married. Having kids. Getting divorced.
那个时候， 还以为你是阅读障碍。
The time that we thought you were dyslexic.
当我教你骑自行车！
When I taught you how to ride a bike.
离婚,,,,,,又来了！ 让我的主人。
Getting divorced again. Getting my master's degree.
终于等到你想要的工作。
Finally getting the job I wanted.
发送到萨曼莎为单向。 UNI。 送你上大学！
Sending Samantha off to college. Sending you off to college.
你知道下面是什么，是吗 我他妈的葬礼！
You know what's next? Huh?
It's my fuckin' funeral!
走开，让我的照片！
Just go! And leave my picture!
没有你走在前面40年
Aren't you jumping ahead by, like, 40 years or something?
我只是觉得,,,,,,会更多。
I just thought there would be more.
松手
不想成为你的英雄
不想成为一个伟大的人
只是想与所有打
您的闹剧
不想成为你的巡游的一部分
每个人都应该有机会
与其他人走
虽然我一直
一项工作是与我的女孩
也许买新的字符串
与她在周末
我们可以私聊的事情
我们的美国梦的秘密
宝宝需要保护
但我是一个孩子和其他人一样
那么，让我去
不想成为你的英雄
不想成为一个伟大的人
只是想打其他人一样
您必须是梅森。
Hey, you must be Mason.
道尔顿，对不对
Yeah. Dalton, right?
如何高兴终于见到您。
Yeah, man, it's nice to finally meet you. Definitely.
请问这一边是对你有好处
Are you cool with this side of the room?
- 是的。 - 我到了早晨，扔那里的一切。
Yeah.
Got in this morning, just moved my shit in, man.
好吧。不用担心。
Well, yeah, I don't care. No worries.
需要带什么帮助箱包
Cool. Can I help you with anything, man?
Any bags, any of that stuff need brought in?
我只能框 并且是很轻的，但,,,
I just got like one box left, I packed pretty light.
- 我感谢你。 - 别客气。
But I appreciate it.
It's my pleasure, man. Of course.
你会去的方向
Um... Are you going to the orientation mixer thing?
介绍会
Orientation mixer thing?
他妈的说！我不会去。 并没有为此事。
Fuck no, man, I'm not going to that,
and neither are you, by the way.
我们有更好的事情要做。
We got way better stuff to be doing, dude. All right.
- 准备好了 - 是啊嘿,,,,,,倒钩。
You ready? Yeah.
我的伴侣 第四个梅森。梅森，倒钩。
Hey, Barb, this is my roommate Mason. Mason, Barb.
- Hi. - Hey.
- 你来和我们一起 - 他们要去哪里
You coming with us?
Where're you going?
- 一日游。 - 是的，我们一起去。
Hiking. Yeah, man, you should come.
如果我们现在离开，我们会看到 日落大弯。你知道吗
If we leave now we can catch the late afternoon at Big Bend.
孩子。
You ever been before, man?
Yeah, but not since I was really little.
更多的理由现在来。 这就是为什么我们在这里。
Then all the more reason to come now, man. That's why we're here, dude.
梅森，她是妮可， 倒钩伴侣。
Oh, Mason, this is Nicole, Barb's roommate.
- 怎么样 - 嗨。
Hey, what's up?
- 梅森，妮可。 - 那又怎样你来吗
Hi. Mason, Nicole.
So, you game?
当然。
Sure.
这里，这个结束。
Here, have the rest of this.
的最佳时机。他贴 当我们到了山上。
Got it timed perfectly. It'll kick in when we get in the mountains.
辣妹！正在进行中。
Awesome. Let's go.
你让主体
Do they let you major in that here?
好吧，这不是那么重要了,,,,,,
Well, it's not that serious here, so I kinda train outside of university,
所以我训练 走出校门，但是,,,
but I'm taking all my basics like History of Dance and all that.
当然，这里所有的基本知识 作为舞蹈史之类的东西。
Nice. Yeah.
你怎么教
What do you teach?
哎呀！好,,,
Oh, gosh.
芭蕾舞，踢踏舞 美国，爵士，嘻哈,,,
Ballet, tap, jazz, lyrical, hip-hop. Wow...
- 你更喜欢哪个 - 跺脚。
Which one's your favorite?
Tap.
你可以发明,,, 你自己的声音和,,,
Yeah? Yeah.
You get to like make up all your own sounds, and there's no rules.
没有规则。有自由创造。
Just like creative freedom.
- 非常好。 - 是的。
That's great. Yeah.
所以，我喜欢教它，然后,,,
That's why I love teaching it, 'cause,
它是如此的美丽对我是 转向在我们这一代。
I don't know, it's so beautiful to me,
and it's kind of dying away in this generation,
帮助回馈给孩子们。
so, to be a part of bringing it back
这是非常有意义的。
to the kids is really rewarding.
Right, keeps it going. Yeah.
- 他们多大年纪了 - 十六
How old are they?
Six to eight. Wow.
不怕 他们是不是害羞的。
Yeah. They have no fear, and they're not self-conscious at all.
尚未到来 在年龄感尴尬。
They haven't reached the awkward years yet.
不，我会来找你。
Yeah, not yet. It's coming.
Hey-
Hey.
道尔顿做疯狂的事情的时候。
Dalton can be crazy sometimes.
看起来不错的人。
He seems cool, though.
是的。是的，两者都是。
Yeah. Yeah, they're both really cool.
你感觉如何
How are you feeling?
好吧。
Great. Pretty great, to be honest.
非常好，其实。
Good.
好吧。
很高兴你加入本集团。
I'm really happy that you're hangin' out with us.
我也是。
Yeah. Me, too.
此刻正有 一个美妙的性高潮！
This moment's having a falsieful whoregasm!
这是因为如果所有的时间过 部署，让我们在这里,,,
It's like as if all of time has unfolded before us
so we could stand here and look out and scream, "Fuck, yeah!"
并期待与呐喊:靠，是啊！
你有没有看到人们如何 总是说“把握当下”
You know how everyone's always saying, "Seize the moment"?
我倾向于认为这是倒退。
I don't know, I'm kinda thinking it's the other way around.
瞬间捕捉我们。
You know, like, the moment seizes us.
是的。
Yeah. Yeah, I know.
是的，当然，是,,,,,,是恒定的。
It's constant. The moment, it's just...
时间是,,,
It's like it's always right now, you know?
这就像永远 出来了，你知道吗
是的。
Yeah.
Subtitle:I scalisto